(This show features indirect advertisements.)
(Running Man)
It is 2026, Seoul.
The richest people in South Korea are here.
(What if you could be in the top 0.01 percent for just one day?)
Can you go to buy supercars...
(He dreams of a one-time cash payment for supercars.)
and say, "Give me all the cars from here to there"?
- Of course, he can. - It's true that I'm rich!
A super-wealthy man who can buy...
(Super-wealthy man, Yu Jae Seok)
an entire supercar dealership, Yu Jae Seok.
The chairman of the company could even come in his underwear.
(A shameless composure to roam the office like a playground)
I'm the chairman's son.
Don't be ridiculous.
A spoiled son of a chairman, Haha.
Hey, this is a designer brand!
(The bigger the logo, the better.)
(Getting defensive over the price)
This is worth 1,400 dollars!
A nouveau riche obsessed with luxury brands, Jee Seok Jin.
(Newly rich late bloomer, Jee Seok Jin)
My parents run a passenger ship company.
Where?
(A maritime silver spoon, Song Ji Hyo)
Tongyeong.
Are all the ships there owned by your parents?
They gather in one place to conspire in money laundering.
(Corrupt tycoons' secret get-rich scheme)
And...
(Setting out to reel in the big catch, the corrupt tycoons)
those tracking them down to stop the money laundering.
- Spy? - He looks scary.
(You cannot escape from him once caught.)
(The snake-eye radar)
- I think he's listening. - Just do it.
A relentless dog that never lets go once it bites, Kim Jong Kook.
(Snake-eyed Chief Kim, Kim Jong Kook)
- This is what I wanted to see. - Don't be so condescending.
(Once he locks horns, he goes until the end.)
Should I go back to my old personality?
Yang Se Chan, recklessly charging ahead.
(Team Detective's point man, Yang Se Chan)
I'm good at finding things, but I'm bad at deduction.
(Her intuition and shamelessness are both at 100 percent.)
Jae Seok would know that.
Ji Ye Eun, confusing people with her shameless gift of gab.
(Shameless profiler, Ji Ye Eun)
- Let's go. - Okay.
("Flex X Cop" in Running Man)
- He looks like a real cop. - I'll catch them all.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Look at this place.
(Today's venue for the opening,)
- Chung-Ang. - Chung-Ang University.
- This is really nice. - It's the best.
(boasting a long and rich history)
- The building looks great. - It's really nice.
It has been a really long time since I last came here.
- This school is 110 years old. - It's the 110th year?
It has such a long history.
- This is... - We don't have rich people here.
- Who is rich here? - Aren't you a nouveau riche?
He is more like a nouveau riche.
- What is all this? - Look at this.
(Seok Sam came wearing fake gold.)
And...
your arms will start itching soon.
That's possible.
(Beware of metal allergy.)
- We are cops. - Who is he?
- Are you a rich man? - Me?
How would I possibly be a cop looking like this?
(Trying to become a rich man by wearing a magician's hat)
What am I, Columbo the detective?
- He's a nouveau riche. - He's so ugly.
(Bang)
- A nouveau riche. - Wait, Jae Seok.
Are you Tae Jin Ah?
This is too much.
(An outfit that's more suited for a dinner show than a supercar)
He doesn't look rich.
- What's that? - By the way,
what kind of rich man are you?
(How do you look like a wealthy man?)
I'm a nouveau riche.
You don't look rich at all. You look like...
She has the Cheongdam-dong vibe.
- Yes, a little... - A rich daughter-in-law.
(The only elegant look among the members)
- Yes, she is... - What are you talking about?
I was born and raised in Cheongdam-dong.
Ji Hyo.
You look good in those shoes with holes now.
The shoes... They are jelly shoes.
(Practical elegance with breathability as a priority)
- Ji Hyo is... - She looks like a daughter-in-law.
Yes. A daughter-in-law who inherited wealth.
- She displays her business acumen. - Ji Hyo, you have...
(Spotted something)
something on your face. Do you want me to take it off?
That's not it. She drew it on purpose.
- What did she draw? - The beauty spot.
- I see. - Gosh, seriously...
(A beauty mark under the eye that fills the empty spot)
- This? - That's a beauty spot.
(Lady Song showed up with a beauty mark.)
Look, Jong Kook. Doesn't it look like she has something on her face?
It just looks...
like a freckle.
(Annoyed)
- Why would you say that? - Don't you think so?
- It can't be a freckle. - I just...
- Why did you... - Listen.
Freckles do not show up as just a single spot like this.
(Thug Chief Kim is already teasing her.)
You're just being mean.
So, today,
are we having guests? I have a feeling that...
- there will be more people. - They're coming.
(Today's guests who will complete the "Flex X Cop" theme)
Someone's coming. Who is it?
- What? - Who are they?
- Rich people? - It's Eun Chae.
- It's Bo Hyun. - Ahn Bo Hyun.
(The real "Flex X Cop" has come to Running Man.)
- It's Bo Hyun. - It's for "Flex X Cop."
Bo Hyun.
(Actor Ahn Bo Hyun)
- Hello. - Bo Hyun.
Hey, Bo Hyun.
- And we have Eun Chae. - Hey.
(Actress Jung Eun Chae)
- Hello, Sang Jun. - How have you been?
(Actor Kang Sang Jun)
- Hello. - And we have Shin Bi here.
(Actor Kim Shin Bi)
Shall we get started now?
("Flex X Cop" is returning stronger with Season 2.)
I am the owner here and a violent crimes detective.
(A 3rd-generation tycoon detective who catches villains with wealth)
The new team leader is coming.
(The newly joined ace team leader)
- Get ready. - She's really tough.
You're not crying, are you?
Detectives do not need secretaries.
(The Violent Crime Team 1 duo who jump in risking their lives)
We found the suspect.
(The new 4 loaded detectives are returning even stronger.)
There's no such thing as a perfect crime.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - It's been a while.
- I'm a big fan. - Nice to meet you.
- It's good to see you. - Eun Chae.
He's just like Jae Seok.
(The scent of a kindred spirit)
- You two look like a couple. - They are similar.
(The orange suit is more suited for a stage performance.)
- Who? - You two.
So, the four of you are doing a new drama?
It's "Flex X Cop 2."
That's why you're here together.
That's why...
(Today's race is with the cast of "Flex X Cop 2.")
we're divided into two teams of tycoons and cops.
I can tell you're the cop.
- That's right. - He's a cop.
(Windbreaker look)
- You're dressed like a cop. - Yes.
- Eun Chae is also a cop. - Yes.
(Eun Chae, wearing leather, is also a detective.)
- She's a cop. - Eun Chae is a cop.
- Obviously, he's a tycoon. - He is.
(Sung Joon, the tycoon with a strong personality)
Like a thug-like tycoon.
He's a rich man who causes a lot of trouble.
- Bo Hyun is also a tycoon. - Yes.
(Bo Hyun, looking neat, is also a tycoon.)
- Bo Hyun looks rich. - Yes.
(Leather shoes giving off rich vibes)
- Look at his shoes. - They look really fancy.
- You look great, Bo Hyun. - Obviously, he looks rich.
Bo Hyun is doing the sequel...
because Season One was successful.
Was there Season One?
(Surprised)
This is Season Two!
- You're driving me crazy. - Hey.
(Walking up to the clumsy one)
I'm sorry.
(Seok Sam)
- You know him. - I didn't know.
(He was here to promote Season 1 2 years ago.)
- It is currently airing. - It is airing.
- So it's "Flex X Cop." - Yes.
Does a detective become a tycoon, or does a tycoon become a detective?
(Seok Sam was confused alone back then too.)
- A tycoon becomes a detective. - I see.
- Are you the tycoon? - The opposite is not easy.
- The drama has already started. - I'm sorry.
- Bo Hyun is the tycoon. - He's rich.
I'm sorry.
(His short-term memory has him feeling bad for two years.)
- He's unbelievable. - I wanted to remind people again.
- I'm really sorry. - Seriously, he knows nothing...
- about what happens in the world. - You didn't know about his album.
- Ye Eun and I released a new album. - It's "Aqua."
- I had no idea. - Right.
- Let's call it even. - It's fine, then.
(They're even.)
- Call it even. - It's fine.
- It doesn't matter now. - It's even.
Eun Chae, is this your first time on Running Man?
- Yes. I rarely... - This is your first time?
- You rarely do variety shows. - It's my first major variety show.
(This is Eun Chae's first-ever variety show appearance!)
- Seriously? - My first TV variety show.
I was a little disappointed.
- Why? - Because you didn't come.
I'm a big fan.
Just try your best to adjust.
- Why are you being so mean? - What are you doing?
(A cheesy tone that blurs the line between...)
(encouragement and intimidation)
- You're intimidating her. - Don't be like that.
- Just trust me. - What's with him?
You better just do what's worth your pay while you're here.
(Time to prove that paycheck is worth it)
Just make sure you do get your job done.
I'll do it eventually.
Worth his pay?
Sang Jun, Shin Bi, is this your first variety show?
- How is it? - Is it your first time?
- It's pretty much my first time. - I see.
- I know, right? - Yes.
It seems like...
you did not sleep well last night.
That's not true.
(Eyes wide open)
- Did you sleep well? - Yes.
Did you not watch the Spain soccer match?
- No. I'm not a big soccer fan. - You didn't watch it.
- You don't like soccer? - No.
Then you'll grow distant from Jong Kook.
(Trembling)
(He declares a distaste for soccer to the future KFA president.)
- You're not a soccer fan? - You don't like it?
Then you'll grow distant from Jong Kook.
What about you, Shin Bi? Did you sleep well?
I was excited about today, so I couldn't sleep well.
(First appearance)
Then, you must've watched soccer.
- I didn't. - You didn't?
(Shin Bi also gets 0 points for soccer.)
Hang on. Shin Bi...
- is from Anyang. - Anyang?
- Shin Bi is from Anyang. - I'm from Anyang.
- Where in Anyang? - In Anyang...
A neighborhood right near where you used to live.
- Near? - Yes.
(I've found my little brother.)
It's done for Shin Bi.
(Anyang brother)
- It's done for Shin Bi. - Anyang?
I also went to Anyang Arts High School.
He went to Anyang Arts High School.
- Anyang Arts High School? - Yes.
- So, you studied in Anyang. - Yes.
- He doesn't seem to care. - So you're from Anyang.
(He prefers the Anyang resident to the Anyang student.)
- Really? - Yes.
(Detective Kim is weak to regional ties.)
It gives him a huge head start.
- We lived right nearby. - Eun Chae.
Where are you from, Eun Chae?
I'm from Busan.
- Busan? - Busan?
Are you from Busan?
(Busan Blowfly greets her automatically.)
- That's fake. - He's not from Busan.
- You know "Busan Vacance," right? - It's fake.
(Mr. Fake Busan asks for a handshake while wearing a suspicious fedora.)
- It's fake. - He's fake.
- We won yesterday. - Yes.
(Baseball)
You're not even from Busan.
I'm an ambassador for Haeundae.
(Impressed by his persistence)
- But they could not sleep. - Really?
- We have a group chat, - Yes.
and they were busy practicing something.
(A personal talent he prepared even losing sleep over?)
- Really? - What did you practice?
Did you practice a dance for the opening?
- I practiced a dance a bit. - I see.
Dance?
(He actually came prepared to show off his talent.)
- You did? - What did you prepare?
- It's b-boying. - B-boying?
I thought he was wearing b-boying shoes.
- I see. - Are you a former b-boy?
- Do you dance? - Yes.
I was in a club back in middle school.
You were in a club.
We should watch it then.
(Everyone is looking forward to it.)
Is the floor okay?
(Checking the floor)
- His outfit is perfect. - The floor is fine.
- Well... - We have music prepared.
(Worried)
- Don't get hurt. - This is amazing.
- Please move aside just a bit. - Okay.
All right. Spread out.
(He confidently appears while requesting a vast stage.)
There you go.
- Okay. - There you go.
(Shin Bi-boy warms up lightly.)
Go.
You're the best.
(Jumping)
- What... - It's not as high as I expected.
(Disappointed)
He jumped gently.
(Dancing)
He's supposed to jump high.
(Fussy footwork)
- This is... - Hey.
What is this?
(Struggling)
- Wait. - Mister.
This is a good one.
- He's good. - Mister.
(Wrapping it up with a decent pose)
- By the way... - Jae Seok, what was that?
But it was a little...
He asked us to move aside,
so I thought he'd spin like three times in the air.
But he just went like this.
(Jumping on the spot)
What was that?
(A surprisingly calm dance for asking for space)
I thought he would do...
a 9 to 9 or windmills.
It looked more like some martial arts moves.
(Grooving in offbeat with his stiff body)
- What was that? - Right.
Why did you tell us to step back?
- I... - Why did you tell us to step back?
(Breathing heavily)
It is because I have never done it in front of so many people.
It is fine to do it like this, though.
It was fun.
- It was fun. - Anyang.
(Everything is okay since he's from Anyang.)
- You all laughed. - It's Anyang.
It was a lot of fun.
(He silences the criticism with the Anyang privilege.)
- That darn Anyang. - Anyang.
He's like that again.
- Thank you, Jong Kook. - He takes care of him.
(Regional ties is the best.)
Actually, I also prepared...
some rap over the original soundtrack...
of our drama yesterday.
- Really? - Rap?
- You rap? - The thing is,
- he used to be a rapper. - Seriously?
(Wingman)
- He was a rapper at YG. - Really?
(The promising rapper had auditioned for YG Entertainment.)
- For real? - You know the agency.
- YG? - He was a rapper at YG?
For a short period of time.
- What was your rap name? - His rap name?
It was MC Deep Black.
(MC Deep Black)
- Deep Black. - Deep Black?
I think I've heard of it.
Deep Black.
Deep Black is...
(Additional information about MC Deep Black)
- Are you married? - the husband of Lee So Na,
- who won "Miss Trot 4." - Really?
(The husband of Lee So Na, the winner of "Miss Trot 4")
- Is your wife the winner? - Yes.
- I see. - Really?
That's impressive.
He and his wife went to a karaoke room yesterday.
(Little fun fact)
Really?
He sent us a photo of them practicing for hours.
- Deep Black? - Deep Black.
(How good is Deep Black, who practiced with his talented wife?)
- This is crazy. - Say, "Microphone check, one two."
- He practiced for hours? - Microphone check, one two.
Let's go!
Slam it into the ears!
- You got this! - I'm so shy.
I'll just give it a try.
It's been ten years.
(A rap performance by Deep Black who got a mic again after 10 years)
Welcome, Deep Black.
I'm sorry. Please let me try it again.
- Try it again? - Why?
(He stops performing after just one measure.)
I'm really nervous.
(What was that?)
He came in on the wrong beat.
- One more time. - Jae Seok, what is this?
- I'm really nervous. - He came in on the wrong beat.
- Just give him one more chance. - Wait.
- What's with those guys? - Hey, Bo Hyun.
(Manager Ahn tries to calm the enraged audience down.)
- Hey. - He told us to step back.
- Just give him one more chance. - Let him try it again.
- One more time. - Okay.
(MC Deep Black got too nervous.)
- One more time! - Deep Black!
- By the way... - What was that?
Deep Black, we don't have much time.
Okay. I get it.
- We're running out of time. - Just one more chance, please.
(After calming down the impatient audience)
- Okay. - Try it again.
(A second chance obtained with difficulty)
(Will Deep Black be able to avoid the pit of fire?)
(Nervous)
Show us, Deep Black!
("Flex X Cop" cypher)
(Shin Bi-boy steps up to support him.)
(Tiny bit of teamwork)
(Still off beat)
(Deep Black pulled it off!)
- Good job. You did well. - You nailed it.
(Praising them)
Deep Black!
- Is this a rock song? - Deep Black.
(An ambiguous genre)
His delivery is a bit poor.
Deep Black cannot come...
(Deep Black cannot come with us.)
- with us. - He can't come with us.
Unfortunately, this is it for Deep Black.
(Ended up in the pit of fire)
All right, Deep Black.
Today, we're having a race with the actors...
from the new SBS drama, "Flex X Cop 2."
It's called the Undercover Flex Versus Cop Race.
Undercover Flex Versus Cop Race?
Team Flex is Yu Jae Seok, Jee Seok, Jin, Haha,
Song Ji Hyo, Ahn Bo Hyun, and Kang Sang Jun.
And Team Detective is Kim Jong Kook, Yang Se Chan,
Ji Ye Eun, Jung Eun Chae, and Kim Shin Bi.
Team Flex has...
one chairman who is hiding their true identity.
Also, there's someone from Team Detective...
- hiding among Team Flex. - What?
- On our team? - An undercover detective?
- Right. - On our team?
- An undercover detective? - Among us?
(Among them are a chairman and an undercover detective.)
- On our team? - Among Team Flex.
Meanwhile, an undercover secretary from Team Flex...
is hiding on Team Detective.
- An undercover secretary. - A secretary?
On Team Detective?
An undercover secretary?
Team Flex will win if the chairman...
manages to escape with the money.
(Team Flex wins.)
However, if Team Detective arrests the chairman,
(Team Flex loses.)
or if Team Flex escapes with the undercover detective...
still in their ranks, Team Flex loses.
(Team Flex loses.)
Okay, got it.
Your objective is to watch out for spies on your team...
and try to figure out who they are.
- Among us? - On the team?
(An undercover detective is hiding on Team Flex.)
- On Team Flex. - An undercover detective.
- On the team? - On Team Flex.
Really?
(The chairman's secretary is hiding on Team Detective.)
(Will they be able to catch the spy on a mission?)
Let's go!
- Over here. - It's raining.
- Over here, guys. - Goodness.
(The first mission will take place in a gym.)
- Wait, what is this? - No way.
Looks like a setup for foot volleyball.
- It's foot volleyball. - No way.
Foot volleyball?
No way.
(Two-left-feet Jong Kook is the first to sit down.)
(Stepping)
(Stepping hard on his foot)
Are you talking about the legendary basketball player?
Hold on, Ji Hyo stepped...
- right on my foot as she walked by. - Hi.
- What's wrong? - I did what?
- When did I do that? - As she was walking by,
(Ji Hyo stepped hard on Kook's foot.)
she stepped on it hard.
Can't the one-percent step on a detective's foot?
- Is that it? - What?
- Is that part of her mission? - Is that a task she has to do?
- Wait. - Is that a mission for her?
That must be a task for her.
(Is stepping on someone's foot her secret mission?)
- She stepped on it hard. - They could have tasks.
Don't Seok Jin's lips look a bit too red?
- Tell me about it. - Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
- What is it? - Your lips are a bit too red.
Is that a task of yours?
- They're too red. - They're bright red.
(Is her Joker-like makeup his secret mission?)
Let me explain.
- Is that blood? - Seriously?
- They're even redder than mine. - They're bright red.
- Is it for real? - I applied something way too red.
- Is that your wife's? - This...
I was looking for my lip balm this morning and...
(It's not a mission.)
(Seok Sam brought his wife's lip balm.)
Please tell me if it looks weird.
- They're too red. - They're bright red.
(Wiping)
- Your lips are too red. - They're really red.
(Jae Seok)
- Your hat says you're the boss. - In the end...
Jae Seok.
- It says boss on your cap. - It says boss.
- You spell boss with a double S. - I know,
- but it's confusing. - Minus the S.
This is for Boston.
Right, it's Boston.
(Knowing that there's a spy,)
Anyway, Bo Hyun spotted that.
There's a spy among us, guys.
(everything and anything looks suspicious.)
(The first mission)
All right. The game is Loose Lips Foot Volleyball.
(Mission 1 of Undercover Tycoons versus Detectives)
- What's that? - It's 4-on-4 foot volleyball.
You can swap out players whenever you want.
The first team to score...
- six points wins. - Okay.
But there's a catch.
You'll lose a point every time you speak English.
- My gosh. - What?
- That's tough. - Really?
We use way more English words than we think.
Especially, "okay."
- I say "okay" a lot. - Same here.
(A fatal rule for Mr. Okay)
Okay!
- We all say "okay" a lot. - Exactly.
There's a benefit for the winning team,
(Only the winning team of the foot volleyball gets a benefit.)
so the spies on each team might try to sabotage things.
(The spy of each team could intentionally troll their own team!)
The spies will probably try to throw the match.
They should if they don't want...
(Each team has 1 spy.)
the team they're on to win the benefit.
- That's right. - We have...
(A chance to figure out who is the hidden spy)
a spy among us.
- Exactly. - There's a spy among us.
I suspect Ji Hyo.
Isn't there a spy on our team too?
Now, please choose the four starting players.
Jong Kook, who should start?
Let's see how good...
- the guests are. - Eun Chae, you're up.
So how about it? Shin Bi and Eun Chae,
(Eun Chae and Shin Bi, the unknown talent, are going to play.)
- go ahead. - Let's see what they can do.
You should know Se Chan is...
(A team of 4 complete with Jong Kook and Se Chan)
pretty decent at foot volleyball.
Even if Jong Kook's the spy, no one will suspect him.
- Right. - He's terrible at soccer and...
I always make people laugh when I play foot volleyball.
(Acting cool)
You've got to be kidding me.
If we play foot volleyball...
with spies on the teams, everyone's going to suspect me.
I can't believe Jong Kook.
(Unable to tell if he's just bad or is the spy)
- Let's see for now. - Okay, let's do this.
The main reason you'll never be the head...
of the soccer association is that you're terrible at soccer.
Bo Hyun, are you good at this?
(Bo Hyun and Jae Seok have played in "Whenever Possible.")
- Me? At foot volleyball? - Yes.
These sneakers are more fashion shoes.
- What? - I see.
Having a wide surface helps though.
(Bo Hyun is making excuses.)
- We'll see how it goes. - The shoes, I mean.
Right. We have Sang Jun too, so...
I can safely say I have two left feet.
It's weird how they're already making excuses.
- But I... - You're saying you're bad at this.
(The two guests are making excuses even before the game has started.)
Oh, no. This is bad.
Like I said, I have two left feet.
It seems strange to me that he's saying this.
Why do you think he's saying he has two left feet?
(Are they making excuses to fulfill their job as a spy?)
- Exactly. - As soon as I blow this whistle,
you'll lose a point if you speak English.
Got it. We can't speak English while playing, right?
That's right. That's minus a point.
You can't say "minus."
Right, I'll say "lose." No way.
(Using English out of habit)
- What am I going to do? - Good catch.
Please make sure you don't say "okay."
(Laying down the law)
Right, don't say it.
(No English starting now)
Hold on. If so, won't the spy...
If so, won't the spy...
Hey. What did you just say?
Just don't speak at all.
(The team lost 1 point as soon as the game started.)
Won't it be too easy for the secret agent to do their thing?
(Writer)
You just lost a point for speaking English.
- Okay! - Why? What did I say?
Okay!
(Mr. Okay causes trouble right away.)
- Jong Kook. - Did you hear Jong Kook?
- Say, "good" instead. - Good!
(Instead of "okay")
(Embarrassed)
Jong Kook loses a point for his team.
(The two teams start by losing 1 point each.)
- Good. - What a mess.
- The game will begin. - Come on.
(The game begins.)
Not being able to use English is killing me.
- Let's go! - Let's go.
(Instead of "fight")
I'll go.
(Starting with Haha's serve)
- Go ahead. - Good!
- Slow and steady. - There you go.
- Eun Chae! - What's wrong?
(Jong Kook with the receive)
Slow and steady.
Good.
(Shin Bi kicks it over the net.)
(The ball heads to Sang Jun, who claims to have two left feet.)
(Groaning)
(Made a mistake looking all clumsy)
- Yes! - Sang Jun, wait.
You weren't kidding, were you?
- I wasn't kidding. - Sang Jun's the weak link.
Isn't the average man better than that?
Sang Jun has two left feet.
- Tell me about it. - Weren't you in the military?
(Brightly)
I didn't play foot volleyball that much.
- You didn't? - No. I was so bad at it.
Okay! He's hopeless.
- He's hopeless. - Jong Kook, please.
(Simply excited)
- He's hopeless. - Jong Kook, you said "okay."
Jong Kook, you spoke English.
- I said "hopeless." - But also "okay."
(Jong Kook loses another point for his team.)
Darn it.
- But... - Again.
(Team Flex: Minus 1, Team Detective: Minus 1)
- It's hard not to talk. - Let's go again!
Here we go.
(The game resumes with Se Chan's serve.)
I shouldn't talk at all.
The game's started.
- Haha... Use your head. - I shouldn't talk.
(The ball goes to Sang Jun.)
Haha... Use your head.
Use your head.
(What?)
(Sang Jun loses a point for them.)
- Hey! - Hey.
(A sudden back header)
(Sang Jun has once again caused trouble.)
Sang Jun has two left feet. We can say it for sure.
- What... - This doesn't make sense.
He's acting strange.
- What... - Isn't he doing this on purpose?
- I'm terrible at this. - Are you faking it?
That's not it.
(Is he really bad at it, or is he doing his spy thing?)
- Wait, is he... - That's really not it.
Something's just off.
Sang Jun, why are you so bad at this?
(Suspicious)
Are you doing this on purpose?
(Deep Black has been marked.)
That's really not it.
How can a guy be this bad at the sport?
(Team Flex: Minus 1, Team Detective: Minus 0)
- We'll give him another chance. - Right, let's see how he does.
- Get ready! - Here we go.
(Se Chan serves again.)
All right. Sang Jun, here you go.
My ball.
- Good. - A gentle tap.
(Off Bo Hyun's pass,)
- Okay! - Nicely done.
(Ji Hyo sends it over with a Taekgyeon kick.)
(Minus 1 point)
- Okay! - Good.
Good.
- Nicely done. - Nice.
(Team Detective is building up.)
- Sorry about that. - Looking good.
- Good! - Yes, good.
Good!
(Hits the net)
(An error by Shin Bi)
What's with all of them?
(The guests)
- Shin Bi. - What's with the whole cast?
(Come here.)
(Summoning him silently)
There are too many secret agents.
- What's with the whole cast? - Are you kidding me?
(A threatening arm around the shoulder)
- That was weird. - But...
(Trembling)
Wasn't that a bit weird?
- I mean, defense... - Right?
(Axe Kim starts doubting his Anyang brother.)
- Us three aren't bad. - We're not doing too bad.
- I messed up my footwork. - Wouldn't...
(Being kind)
- Wouldn't a header be better? - Right.
Like this. Plant a header.
(Demonstrating)
- Got it. - If the height isn't right.
- Got it. - Okay! Oh, no!
Okay! Oh, no!
(Jong Kook said "okay" again.)
Are you kidding me?
- Jong Kook! - Jong Kook, please.
Jong Kook, you said "okay" three times already.
Jong Kook, aren't you saying it too often?
(Being honest)
Is there something to bite down on?
- His shirt. - Don't do that.
(Gagging himself up)
What is it?
You really can't help it.
Go.
(The game resumes.)
All right. Whose ball?
(The ball drops in the middle.)
Whose ball?
(Another back header!)
(The ball goes out.)
Are you serious?
What... Is this for real?
Who on earth is he?
(Sang Jun has already lost 3 points.)
- Thank you so much. - He tops all the guests...
we've had so far.
- Is he a secret agent? - He tops everyone.
You're a gem.
- You... - Sang Jun, you're out.
- I mean... - Sang Jun, sit this out.
- Seriously. - Can he really be this bad?
(Subbing out Player Kang, who is being suspicious)
Is this for real?
- It's for real. - How can you be this helpless?
(Team Flex: Minus 1, Team Detective: Minus 0)
- This doesn't make any sense. - It's for real.
Just go for it.
(Play resumes with Jong Kook's serve.)
Haha, go ahead.
(Haha's good receive)
- Just send it over. - Kick it.
(Bo Hyun barely manages to send it over.)
(Se Chan's toss)
- What's going on? - Go for it.
(Eun Chae sends it over!)
(Laughing)
- Good! - Nice one, Eun Chae.
(It's Team Flex's turn again.)
(Bo Hyun's back header!)
(Yelp!)
(Nice back header!)
- Nice. - Good job.
(Yelp!)
(Even she finds it funny.)
- Nice. - Hold on.
You looked like you were doing Taekwondo.
(Her kick was pretty decent.)
Nice one, Eun Chae.
Eun Chae's pretty good at this.
(Haha serves once again.)
This one's Jong Kook's.
- My ball. - Shin Bi.
(Se Chan's stable toss)
- It's Eun Chae. - Go, Eun Chae.
- Eun Chae. - Calm and steady.
(Screaming)
(Eun Chae's surprise sole kick)
(She scores!)
(Incredible!)
- She kicked with her sole. - She kicked it like this.
(Eun Chae takes the ball down with a single front kick.)
How can one kick with their sole?
Eun Chae, what was that scream?
(Screaming)
(Basically Sharapova of foot volleyball)
- She's getting better at this. - Exactly.
How can one kick with their sole?
Hold on. Why isn't Ye Eun playing?
(Team Flex: 0, Team Detective: 1)
Ye Eun, come on in. We're in the lead.
(Player Ddochi joins when the team is leading by 1 point!)
We need to do better than this.
Haha, go high.
(Haha's serve)
Let's kick it in hard.
(What?)
What's wrong with you?
That was really offensive.
- We'll catch up in no time. - That was offensive.
Ye Eun, that was unique.
(Everyone's stunned by her first touch.)
What's wrong with you?
- You can't do that. - Right, my arm.
- You can't use your arms. - Really?
(That's a given.)
- Do you want to sit this out? - Use this instead.
- Use this. - Haha, how does that make sense?
Give it right here. Haha!
(Team Flex: 1, Team Detective: 1)
- Does this make sense? - What are you doing?
Sorry. It would've gone out.
(Haha serves again.)
Exactly.
Shin Bi, take your time.
(Strong smash from Shin Bi)
(The ball is out.)
- Good job! - Well done!
(Laughing)
- Well done. - He's not bad at foot volleyball,
(Team Flex: 1, Team Detective: 2)
but Shin Bi is all over the place.
He goes overboard.
He's good, but he's all over the place.
He could just do this,
- but he goes... - His body goes...
(Overacting)
- And also... - Didn't he do this beforehand?
He doesn't just run up to the ball.
Shin Bi, take your time.
(Here goes!)
(He's my brother.)
- He does well. - He does.
- He's good. - He's good.
Okay, then. Let's go!
- Come on! - Let's win!
Come on!
(The match resumes as they chant.)
Let's go! Let's win!
Okay. Don't mess up.
Okay!
(Good cover by Jong Kook)
- Shin Bi! - What...
Shin Bi!
(He zooms in and smashes it again!)
(Haha keeps the ball in the air!)
(Jae Seok sent it back over!)
Good job!
(What?)
(Angry mumbling)
(The desperate jump was in vain.)
Jong Kook...
(Look at him.)
Good job!
(Shouting)
(Laughing)
That was impossible.
(Justifying his mistake)
Well done.
- That was a lack of skill. - That was impossible.
He's not undercover. He's just bad at this.
That was impossible. The ball went too far.
(No one is suspecting Jong Kook.)
- He lacks the skill. - He lacks the skill.
(Laughing)
- You're just bad. - That was impossible.
(Mumbling)
It's not about skill.
Let's play!
(Team Flex: 2, Team Detective: 2)
- Come on! - Let's have fun!
(Haha serves again.)
- Head the ball. - Eun Chae!
(Jong Kook covers yet again.)
- Go right for it. - Okay!
(It went over the net!)
(Team Flex is defending well.)
- Sang Jun. - No!
Here it comes.
(Screaming)
That's it.
(A header home-run)
Well done!
(Her slapstick is so entertaining.)
(Dizzy)
- I love your style, Eun Chae. - She's good.
Eun Chae, does your skull protrude to the sides?
- I love it, Eun Chae. - There's a curve!
Eun Chae's awesome.
She doesn't shy away.
(Team Flex: 3, Team Detective: 2)
We just need one lucky shot.
(Team Flex's Bo Hyun serves.)
Let's keep it going.
- Go on! - Let's keep it going.
- This ball... Yes. - It's mine!
(Shouting)
- Yes. - Eun Chae!
(Another headbutt!)
(But the ball is in!)
Is it Eun Chae or me?
Get it over the net!
(It was close, but they lost the point.)
(Team Flex scored scores back-to-back points.)
Come on!
- Good job! - Eun Chae's awesome at this.
(It seems Eun Chae is enjoying doing slapstick comedy.)
- Eun Chae... - She uses her head well.
(Everyone praises her.)
- She's good. - That's awesome.
We won't let you off now!
Send it over.
(Team Flex: 4, Team Detective: 2)
We need just one point.
(Jong Kook's serve went deep.)
- Do it. - This is a tough one.
- This is a tough one. - Well done.
(Haha took it well.)
- It'll go far. - Go.
Nice job.
- Well done. - Come on.
- Good! - Good save.
Eun Chae!
(It's the first decent rally!)
Nice job.
(Which team will win this close match?)
Come on.
(We won.)
- It went over. - It touched, didn't it?
(Jae Seok's foot)
He touched the ball.
(It didn't make contact!)
He didn't touch the ball.
The ball made contact.
- I grazed it. - It touched.
- It touched. - It touched.
(It's Team Jae Seok's point if his foot made contact!)
- He didn't touch the net. - Didn't touch it.
In one go!
(He touched the ball.)
- It touched. - It touched.
(VAR confirms Team Flex's point!)
- I heard it. - He touched it.
- It touched. - It touched.
- Rewind the camera. - He kicked it.
(Writer: "You lose a point for saying 'camera.'")
You lose a point for saying "camera."
- Who said it? - Seok Jin.
Darn you.
(My gosh)
Get out.
(Seok Sam complained only to lose a point.)
- Good job! - Sorry.
You act like you're fluent in English!
(Team Flex: 4, Team Detective: 2)
Why do you use so much English?
(Team Flex needs 2 more points to win again.)
It's pointless if we use English. We mustn't speak English.
(Bo Hyun will serve.)
- Let's not speak English. - I'll serve.
- Here goes. - I'm really sorry.
I really...
- Ahn Bo Hyun! - I really...
(Service error)
Ahn Bo Hyun!
I was trying to be nice.
(Suspicious)
Bo Hyun would do that?
Give him another chance.
(Give him another chance.)
What? Ask politely, then.
(What?)
- "Please give us another chance." - Come on...
Show us the crown of your head.
Give me another chance.
(With no hesitation)
Again. What was that?
Ask politely.
(Hurry up and bow.)
I'm sorry.
- Good. - Okay.
- Politely. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Wait.
- Jong Kook. - What?
What did you say as you turned around?
- The word starting with O. - No.
- Jong Kook, you said "okay." - I didn't.
- You did. - Me?
- You said it. - We can't talk at all.
(Team Flex: 4, Team Detective: 1)
- I said that? - Let's go.
(Okay Man loses a point after a while.)
That's how often we use English.
Bo Hyun, you get another shot.
(They gave him another chance, and he goes back to serve.)
- Here goes. - Here we go.
- Bo Hyun. - Bo Hyun!
(Another service error)
How many secret agents are there?
Why does he keep on...
(There are two secret agents on our team.)
There are two secret agents.
Sang Jun and Bo Hyun are definitely the ones.
(Each team has one spy.)
- The secret agents. - Gosh, this is...
(Could one of them be the spy?)
- It makes no sense. - We can't identify them.
(Team Flex: 4, Team Detective: 2)
- Here goes. - Play on!
Let's play.
(Team Flex serves.)
- Nice one. - Give me a chance.
Good job. Eun Chae!
Let's go, Eun Chae!
(Eun Chae's kicks are fine.)
Nice! Ji Hyo!
(Ji Hyo kicks it just as well,)
Come on.
(and Shin Bi sends it over the net!)
Ji Hyo, head it!
Haha.
(The ball's in the air!)
(Sang Jun hustles over to cover!)
Come on!
Save it!
Go, Sang Jun!
(Can he clear his name and prove his worth?)
Save it!
(Whiny grunt)
(Failed to save the ball)
(Team Flex: 4, Team Detective: 3)
Good job.
(Shin Bi helps Team Detective score!)
- He's good. - Eun Chae did well.
From what I see, Sang Jun is just bad at this.
(Sang Jun's mistake cost them a point.)
Is he really just bad?
You're currently tied at four points each.
(Team Flex: 4, Team Detective: 4)
Come on, team.
(The 1st team to score 2 more points wins!)
Let's do our best and win.
- We need just two points. - Have fun?
Have fun. Let's do this!
(Which team will win the reward?)
Looking good. We can win.
(Haha serves at a crucial moment.)
Jong Kook.
(Trying to disturb her)
It's Eun Chae.
- Take your time. - Eun Chae!
(Eun Chae sends the ball deep!)
- Eun Chae. - Take your time.
- Good job. - Eun Chae...
You're good!
Ji Hyo!
(They score!)
(Team Flex: 4, Team Detective: 5)
(Eun Chae brings her team to match point!)
Good job!
Ji Hyo!
(Gosh...)
It's okay. It was a tough play.
(If Team Detective scores 1 more point, they win!)
My legs didn't reach the ball.
- What a shame. - It was a tough one.
(If Team Flex gives up even 1 point, they lose.)
Just one more point...
It's over.
We can win. Let's give it our all and win.
(This could be the final ball.)
It's doable.
- We can do it. - It's playable.
Focus!
(Team Detective serves.)
- Let's keep it fun. - Me.
Keep it fun.
What on earth?
- Me. - Keep it fun.
(And Just like that, Team Flex lost.)
Darn.
(Even the winners feel bad about celebrating.)
(He played terribly.)
What was that?
What really was that?
I just...
- I meant to... - Use your feet.
(A lame excuse)
Listen. It was a bad bounce.
(Reasonable suspicion)
I think they are the secret agents.
Team Detective wins 6 to 4.
Okay!
(Satisfied)
- That was so annoying. - I'm so frustrated.
- It was fun. - Eun Chae...
isn't the spy.
- You did well. - I tried hard.
You're pretty good.
(Eun Chae's unexpected performance took the suspicion off her.)
Eun Chae did great.
Out of all the guests,
- she's the best. - She's really good.
Team Detective won.
You get a hint about the chairman.
Oh, gosh. That's perfect.
The chairman, not the secretary?
(It's a huge advantage for Team Detective,)
- That's for them. - We must identify them.
(who has to arrest the chairman.)
I have a feeling you're the secret agent.
Sang Jun. You're naming me after how you played?
But Sang Jun...
- I'm hurt. - For a secret agent,
you played consistently badly, so that doesn't make sense.
I don't think Sang Jun's it.
He was enlisted. He must've played a lot of foot volleyball.
(The spies must've made a move while they were doing the mission.)
- Yes. - Gosh. I'm upset.
(Will they be able to catch the spies?)
- Why do they doubt me? - Everyone's suspicious.
A hint about the chairman...
- will be given to Team Detective. - Okay.
They get it now?
We can shorten the list.
Yes. It helps to lose even one candidate.
Even one is huge.
- It's about the chairman? - Yes.
(What kind of clue about the chairman will they get?)
- Come over. - Yes.
(The hint about the chairman)
Here we go.
- What's this? - Okay...
(The chairman's opening outfit included something black.)
- You can tell from the outfit. - Obviously, he's a tycoon.
(The tycoons wore various outfits.)
He is a tycoon.
(The chairman's opening outfit included something black.)
- It's too hard. - This is too vague.
- Yes. It's tough. - It's usually...
(Trying to piece his memories together)
It's not Sang Jun.
(They exclude Sang Jun's flashy outfit?)
Talk to us, Ye Eun.
- Tell us, and we'll share ours. - We want to know...
(Team Flex asks them to share the hint.)
who the chairman is.
- Shall I tell them? - Jong Kook.
- We'll watch their faces. - Okay.
- See how they react. - Their expressions.
(Team Detective wants to share the hint...)
The chairman's opening outfit...
(and read their reactions to figure out the culprit.)
included something black.
- What? - There's no black.
- The opening segment. - The opening segment.
(Looking intently)
Sang Jun's outfit had no black.
The bottom of my shoes was black.
What?
(Did Sang Jun's outfit include black as well?)
- Let's keep watching. - For now...
- Let's watch them. - This is now...
I was black from head to toe.
- You wore something striped. - Yes.
Out of you, only Sang Jun...
- I didn't wear black. - What about you?
- No black at all. - I think there was something.
(Bo Hyun claims that he didn't wear black.)
Your shoes were black.
- No. - Your shoes were black.
- Yes. - Right.
You wore black shoes.
(Bo Hyun was wearing shining black shoes.)
- The shoes were black. - Black shoes.
It's almost everyone.
- It's almost everyone. - They act so nonchalantly.
(His instincts kick in.)
It's really not me. I swear.
(Is Bo Hyun the chairman who is acting?)
- You looked anxious. - I forgot.
I thought I didn't wear black.
We excluded one person.
- We can exclude two! - How so?
Ji Hyo.
- Oh, you're... - She didn't wear anything black.
- She didn't wear anything black. - I think there was black.
- Her shoes? - There was black.
- What is it, Ye Eun? - Wait...
- Her shoes? - The beauty mark on her face?
- Yes! - No!
- No. Listen. - My gosh...
(Jong Kook was talking about outfits,)
(then changed the subject to moles.)
- It's not like that. - It could be her.
(Certain)
- Because... - Her beauty mark.
- That's not it. - Why else would she draw it?
- No! - We found the person!
- Why... - We found the person!
(Is his beauty mark a hint that he's the chairman?)
- Seriously. - We found the person.
- No. - We found the person.
You found the person already?
Who was the first person...
to mention it?
When we were talking during the opening,
(Staring)
we asked what she drew on her face.
She said she drew a fake beauty mark.
- It seems pretty certain. - It didn't make sense.
It seems certain.
- The spy. - Why would she draw a beauty mark?
I think it's certain that you're the spy.
(Shin Bi is suspicious of Jong Kook for insisting the mole is evidence.)
Me?
- Why is it suddenly me? - I think you're certainly the spy.
Me? Suddenly?
- You're... - This is a very insightful point.
- Really? - Yes.
- No. - That's a crucial clue.
(Right)
- It's a crucial clue. - Really?
Secretary Kim, thank you.
(Is Spy Kook stirring up confusion or is Detective Kim onto something?)
- What? - Thank you, Secretary Kim.
The chairman...
has to remove the bomb attached to the briefcase...
and complete the money laundering...
in order to take the money.
If you cut the wrong wire,
Team Detective will receive an additional clue about the chairman.
The chairman will set off...
(Once they split up, the chairman will secretly launder the money.)
after Team Flex members have split up.
(Who is the chairman hiding his identity?)
I have no clue.
It's too early to start making deductions.
Foot volleyball...
didn't give me any clues.
Who do you think is the chairman?
I think it's Bo Hyun.
(I think Bo Hyun is the chairman.)
Sang Jun...
is just cheerful.
(Even when giving the other team a point, Sang Jun...)
Sang Jun!
(Cheerful)
You're really bad with your feet.
- Seriously. - Look closely.
He seems comfortable. He wasn't given a role.
(Seok Jin's deduction: Sang Jun is cheerful because he has no mission.)
Either Bo Hyun or Haha.
(The chairman is either Bo Hyun or Haha!)
I'm certain of it.
(Seok Jin's deduction: It's either Bo Hyun, who is acting,)
Haha or Bo Hyun.
(or Haha, who was dressed in all black.)
One of these two...
is the chairman.
(Meanwhile, Bo Hyun, the possible chairman, is...)
Ji Hyo...
doesn't have a beauty mark on her face.
But she drew one today.
(Like Jong Kook, he's suspicious of Ji Hyo.)
It means she's onto something.
Jae Seok...
is the boss.
- Am I being filmed? - Yes.
- Are you filming me right now? - Yes.
(He's suddenly worried about filming.)
I think Jae Seok is the boss.
(Feeling relieved, he continues his deductions.)
The word "BOS" was written on his cap.
(He's suspicious of Jae Seok's cap with "BOS" on it.)
It's a Boston cap,
but it had "BOS" written on it.
My fandom's name is BOSS.
(His deductions keep going off track.)
He's the boss.
(Meanwhile, the chairman quietly moves alone.)
Here it is.
If I cut the wrong wire, they'll get a hint about me.
(He arrives at the bomb room where he can launder the money.)
Please cut 1 of these 7 wires.
Is it the black one?
Deep black?
I feel sweaty.
I think they'll suspect me because I'm sweating.
One...
(If the bomb goes off, a hint about the chairman will be given!)
(Did the chairman manage to cut the bomb wire?)
It's giving me chills! This is scary!
Did you do well?
(Team Flex comes back after laundering the money.)
- Yes. - Did you cut the right wire?
It's me.
(I'm the chairman.)
(His radar is active.)
The chairman...
(The result of the chairman's money-laundering attempt)
- He cut it? - just successfully removed...
one of the bomb wires.
I guess the chairman got scared.
Since the chairman succeeded, you won't get any additional hints.
I don't think it's Bo Hyun.
- I think it's Sang Jun. - Really?
- We don't know it yet. - We've somehow narrowed it down.
(Will he successfully launder the money without being caught?)
- It's still uncertain. - It's uncertain.
What's that?
- I wonder what we'll do now. - What is this?
Lunch is on the line in this mission, and it's called...
- Chicken Odd or Even. - What mission is that?
(Lunch Mission: Chicken Odd or Even)
We placed a random number of chicken pieces...
in a chicken box.
Each team will guess...
whether the number of chicken pieces is odd or even.
The team that guesses correctly...
- will get to eat the chicken. - No!
Did you fill in the box?
We randomly filled in the box.
It's normally an odd number.
Do you know the answer?
(How many pieces of chicken are inside?)
We know the answer.
- Odd. - Why?
I just have a feeling that it's an odd number.
- I think it's an odd number. - Odd?
- Odd number. - We also think it's an odd number.
(Eun Chae also hopes it's an odd number.)
You think it's an odd number, Eun Chae?
- Are you sure? - Odd number.
- What about Shin Bi? - Odd.
Odd number?
- I also think it's an odd number... - An odd number?
because Shin Bi is quite good at guessing these things.
(Both teams made the same choice.)
Sang Jun, why don't you say it...
in a rap?
Tell them how determined we are to choose odd.
- Deep Black? - Deep Black.
We're going with odd, man!
Shut it!
- Shut it! - Did you say "shut it?"
- That's a little... - I'm sorry.
(The Shut Up Guy ends up being told to keep quiet.)
- "Shut it?" - "Shut it."
Hey...
- What are you doing, Deep Black? - I...
- messed up the rap earlier, so... - Deep Black?
- Deep Black. - Deep Black.
- Black? - Deep Black?
Deep Black?
(Is Sang Jun, whose name includes "Black" the chairman?)
- Are you the chairman? - Seriously...
- It's weird. - I'm not the chairman.
(Suddenly getting suspicious)
- His name is Deep Black. - Deep Black.
(Who is Deep Black, whose rap skills are raising even more suspicion?)
Let's just play rock-paper-scissors.
(They'll play rock-paper-scissors to decide.)
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- That's decided, right? - Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook versus Seok Jin)
Seriously!
Won't you stand up?
(Putting his hands on his hips)
You should sit down as well!
Sit down as well!
(A battle of pride begins.)
Okay.
(Being super childish)
Do it while lying down.
(With a combined age of 110, they play rock-paper-scissors.)
Ready or not,
- rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors!
Okay!
(Seok Jin won.)
- Jee Seok Sam did it. - Okay.
Should we go with odd?
(Team Flex picks odd.)
- I won this one. - Odd number?
(Team Detective automatically chooses even.)
- Good. - Going with even is better.
Going with even is better.
You can count the chicken pieces.
(Checking the number of the chicken pieces)
- It would feel great if it's even. - Odd!
Why does it feel like it will be an even number?
It looks so good.
(Will it be odd or even?)
- Odd. - One.
- Even. - Even.
- Odd. - Odd.
(Even, odd)
- It looks good. - Even.
- Odd. - It looks good.
- Even. - Even.
- Odd. - Normally,
- Even. - it's odd, so it'll be even here.
Clap.
- Odd. - Odd.
- Even. - Even.
- Odd, even. - Don't count them with your eyes.
(Even, odd)
- Odd, even! - Odd, even!
(Picking up speed)
- Odd. - Odd.
(Will it be an odd number?)
- Even! - Even!
(Or an even number?)
- Odd, even! - Odd, even!
(There's one piece remaining.)
- Odd! - Odd!
- Even! Odd! - Even! Odd!
(Team Flex, who chose odd, wins!)
- How did you know? - I had a feeling it would be odd.
How did you guess that it was odd?
(Screaming)
How did you know?
I had a feeling it would be odd.
(Disappointed)
Team Flex wins.
Nice.
(Only Team Flex, the winning team, will get to have lunch.)
Team Flex will get the chicken...
- since you won. - Okay!
- Chicken... - Help yourselves.
(Eating right away)
- Go ahead. - The flesh...
It's really crispy.
We'll set the table for you.
(He's eating it next to Eun Chae on purpose.)
- This is good. - It's really crispy.
- Enjoy the chicken. - Nice.
(A must-have dish at a gathering of the wealthy elite)
- It's really crispy. - This is really tasty.
It's really crispy.
Should I have it with the sauce?
(Dipping it in the sauce)
(Crunch!)
(He has expert-level deboning skills.)
Hey!
It's good.
- Try it with the sauce. - It's really tasty.
(It's a feast fit for the tycoons. They get one whole chicken each.)
Jong Kook...
It's good.
(CEO Ha, the owner of a BBQ restaurant, is satisfied.)
The sauce really balances out the greasiness.
It doesn't feel greasy.
It's really crispy, isn't it?
This is good.
Dip it in the sauce and...
(After rapping for the first time in a while, he's devouring it.)
The sauce tastes amazing.
- It's really crispy. - It's hard to get it this crispy.
This is quite popular among children.
(While the tycoons are enjoying the chicken,)
- This is good. - It's really crispy, isn't it?
(Ddochi feels sad.)
- It's good. - It's not greasy.
This is good.
(The detectives are just smacking their lips.)
What a shame.
I really know how to enjoy chicken.
Right. The foodie is sitting right here.
(Tragic)
We're really good at eating chicken.
(Smacking her lips)
Aren't you going to have some?
Will you give us?
- It won't be for free. - Okay.
Perhaps you could do...
another round of breakdancing like Shin Bi did.
Let's do some breakdancing.
(Springing)
Let's do it.
Do you know that Jong Kook used to be a breakdancer?
I used to back in the day.
- Jong Kook used to do breakdancing. - When I was young.
(A former Anyang dance club member known for his "threshold dance")
If you do some breakdancing, we'll give you some chicken.
(It's not a bad offer.)
- We'll do one set. - One set. Okay.
Let's do this...
(Team Detective is busy getting ready to perform.)
and then do this.
(Working hard)
We'll do this...
It's so funny seeing Eun Chae there.
(Anticipating)
- Four times. - Are you ready?
Music, cue.
(The breakdancing lunch show begins.)
Let's...
Shall we watch them?
(They start by circling around.)
Circle around.
That's cute!
(They're blushing in embarrassment.)
- One, two, three, four! - One, two, three, four!
(She's stumbling right from the beginning.)
(Dongducheon's floor cleaner)
What is this?
Nice.
Nice!
(Anyang Kim Ax)
(Instead of his slower footwork, he's going with finger moves.)
We have to spin now.
Do that move.
(Anyang's Peach Shin Bi)
(He shows off properly this time.)
(The tall sisters)
That's right. Your legs.
Nice. Eun Chae is doing well.
(She's kicking the air as hard as she can.)
- Good! - Nice.
(Spinning)
Ye Eun as well. She's doing well.
Good.
One, two, three!
- Okay! - Okay!
(The quick breakdancing show ends.)
Will you really give them?
- Can we really have some? - Get one piece each.
(He pays them in chicken.)
- Thank you. - Get a big piece.
This sauce is the kick.
(Offering the sauce)
- Thank you. - It's good.
(He's become generous after becoming a tycoon.)
- Here. - Is this a chicken drumette?
(Team Detective finally gets a bite of the chicken as well.)
This sauce is the kick.
The wings are good too.
(Exclaiming)
- It's good. - It's good.
(Speaking at the same time)
(A beastly eating show of the protein killer)
(He debones the piece with his protruding mouth.)
It's good!
- I keep hearing the crunchy sound. - Right.
(Both teams enjoyed the chicken together.)
This is good.
- I'm full. - We enjoyed the chicken.
The last mission with the hint...
is called the Flex of the Tycoons.
(Mission 2: The Flex of the Tycoons)
- What mission is it? - I guess we're going to buy things.
Each team will receive one card...
containing the same amount of money.
The team that guesses the card limit...
(150 dollars, 200 dollars)
and buys the most expensive item wins.
(Payment amount: 150 dollars, Payment amount: 200 dollars)
(Win)
If the card limit is exceeded during payment,
(500 dollars)
the mission fails immediately.
(Fail)
Will it be the price of just one item?
The price of one item must be the highest.
(Even if they buy multiple items, only the most expensive one counts.)
- Will we take what we buy? - No.
- During payment... - He wants to buy batteries again.
(The household essentials enthusiast is taking this chance to stock up.)
Windshield washer fluid and batteries.
- Essentials. - Essentials.
The items you buy...
will go to the final winning team.
The spy will try to exceed the limit.
- That's possible. - That's possible.
What happens if we exceed the limit in the first try?
We won't get to buy anything?
(If their card explodes on their first purchase,)
You fail. Right.
(they immediately fail the mission.)
- Are you the chairman? - We should... Pardon?
- The chairman... - That's also possible, right?
(The spy may try to go above the limit to sabotage the mission.)
Yes.
It's a possibility.
If the secretary gets the card,
the secretary will buy something that exceeds the limit.
- Right. - You're right,
- but then they'll get caught. - Of course.
(They should watch out for who the spy is.)
The secretary is going to try to bait us.
The teams will move out together...
- and start purchasing. - Okay, let's go.
Do you know what I hate? The obvious numbers.
- I bet it's over 100 dollars. - Like 50, 100, and 150.
- It won't be that. - I doubt that'll be the case.
(Se Chan thinks the card limit won't be a round number.)
- I doubt it. - I hate things like that.
- Eun Chae, what's your take on it? - What do you think?
- What's your guess? - How much do you think it'll be?
I think it'll be low.
- A low number? - Really?
- Wait. - Is it you?
(Are you the spy?)
- What do you mean? - No?
She thinks the number will be low.
- She can't be the spy. - Why not?
Because she thinks the number will be low.
(Jong Kook's deduction: The spy will buy something expensive...)
She won't buy enough to go over the limit.
(to go over the limit.)
But a cheaper item...
(Smart)
- We'll lose. Yes, you're right. - Yes, we'll lose.
(Is Eun Chae, who thought the limit would be low, the spy?)
You're right. We'll lose if our item is cheaper.
- Exactly. - Right.
I believe we have to spend at least 100 dollars.
At least 100?
How else are we supposed to win?
(Se Chan thinks they should spend a large amount to win.)
- Are you the undercover secretary? - I doubt it'll be over 100 dollars.
(Suspecting Se Chan right away)
Shin Bi, give me a break, will you?
- Is this your task as a secretary? - Of course not.
Jong Kook, hear me out.
If we only spend 30 to 50 dollars...
- and lose... - That's not enough.
They're going to spend a decent amount of money.
- It can't be 30 to 50 dollars. - They gave us this card to use.
(Shin Bi is suspicious of Se Chan who wants to make a big purchase.)
It's not right to only spend it...
- on something small. - Exactly.
It'll be so annoying if we lose to the other team...
by only buying something small.
- You see, earlier... - I'd rather spend over the limit.
(It's better to spend over the limit?)
By buying something small...
- By buying something small... - Don't we lose our chance...
if we spend over the limit?
- That's right. - It's game over.
- He said that was better. - We'd lose the game.
(Suspicious)
- Who said that? - I'd rather spend over the limit.
- Me? - Yes, you said that.
(Detective Shin Bi is putting pressure on him.)
- You just said so. - That's just how I feel.
Let's say we lost after only spending 30 dollars.
What if we lost after not spending enough?
(Viper eyes)
You'd be better off taking a beating from me.
(Kim Thug is undercover as a detective.)
- You're killing me. - That could be better.
Just hear me out.
I'm saying if we're going to lose,
it'll feel better to lose after going over the limit.
- If that's the case? - Not spending enough...
- and losing to them... - Rather than spending less?
- You're focusing on how it'll feel. - Exactly.
(He narrowly escaped suspicion.)
- That's where my focus is. - I see.
Nothing gets past Shin Bi.
(While Shin Bi, a great detective, is investigating...)
He questions everything we say.
- Keep it up, then. - Right.
- By the way... - Yes, Seok Jin?
Since Bo Hyun plays a detective in the show,
would he really play one again with us?
I'm not the spy.
- They don't give me any tasks. - Really?
Wouldn't one of the guests have a special role today?
- Absolutely. - Of course.
- I'm sure of it. - It's not me.
- I agree. - I think it's Bo Hyun.
- Sang Jun, isn't it you? - It's not me.
It was a little upsetting...
since they didn't give me a role to play,
(His 2nd appearance on Running Man)
even though I thought it was about time.
- By the way, - Really?
the chairman must be feeling lonely,
but you can trust me.
- Chairman. - Tell me whatever is bothering you.
(They're trying to butter up the chairman in the meantime.)
- Thank you, Chairman. - Chairman.
- Chairman... - I don't know who you are but...
Doesn't the chairman need to get out safely today?
How is the chairman supposed to do that?
You can open the door and just get out.
(The chairman has to jump out of the moving car.)
- I'm asking because... - Open the door and...
(Perfect teamwork)
- You'll know how, right? - Say you're escaping.
- Say you're escaping. - Exactly.
- Eject! - Eject.
And hop out.
(It looks like a huge escape scene is coming up.)
Let's buy something we can take home.
(Team Detective arrives at a nearby shopping district.)
Let's go. Let's see what our options are.
- We'll... - How about a door lock?
- What? - I mean...
- Wait, the door lock? - How about a door lock?
(He immediately found a practical item for everyday life.)
- That's expensive. - I should get a new one.
It'll be nice to get a new one.
(Ssaebssaeb's wish list: Door lock)
- Jong Kook. - A rice cooker?
- How about an AC outdoor unit? - An AC outdoor unit?
(Ssaebssaeb's wish list: Door lock, AC outdoor unit)
What about a hair dryer?
(Ssaebssaeb's wish list: Door lock, AC outdoor unit, hair dryer)
Jong Kook, there's a gold exchange shop.
Wait. Gold sounds nice!
(Ssaebssaeb's wish list: Door lock, AC outdoor unit, hair dryer, gold)
We can buy about a gram of gold.
(Gold?)
- Jong Kook. - We're at the SBS building.
- Hey, there's the duvet store. - How about a duvet?
(They spot a bedding store.)
- I actually need one. - I need one too.
- I really need one. - I...
- I really need a duvet. - Jong Kook.
(Those who live alone are excited to see the bedding store.)
- Just this once. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's go.
(They enter the bedding store.)
- Hello. - What's your most expensive duvet?
Can you show us something a little under 100 dollars?
(The estimated limit is 100 dollars.)
- One hundred dollars? - Something...
along those lines. That's right.
(They're looking for something that is less than 100 dollars.)
- This is pretty cute. - A single, maybe?
- This print is cuter. - I know.
(He found something.)
This is European-style.
- Check this out. - This is way cuter.
(The floral lace blanket is exactly Jong Sook's style.)
- This is cute. - Isn't this cute?
Isn't this a tablecloth?
- It's on the thicker side. - It has some weight to it.
(Loving it)
- It's pretty thick. Yes, it's cute. - Cute, right?
- Isn't it cute? - Isn't this for babies?
- This is way cuter. - This must be for babies.
This is 70 dollars.
(Employee: "It's 70 dollars.")
- See? It's expensive. - That's pricey.
(It's under the estimated limit of 100 dollars.)
- The print's adorable. - I know.
(He can't take his eyes off it.)
This is really cute.
- Seventy dollars? - We can play...
- rock-paper-scissors. - Exactly.
- The winner takes it. - The winner can take it.
We can play rock-paper-scissors for it.
Eun Chae, isn't this something you like?
Isn't it?
(Busted)
- Something more elegant? - What do you think?
- What's your vibe? - I'll just flip it over.
- What? - You prefer plain styles.
(Nodding)
Your style is more modern.
(Eun Chae doesn't like floral patterns.)
Meanwhile, this...
- This is more Ye Eun. - It's more Ye Eun.
- Let's keep this as an option. - Let's do that.
- Sure. - Can we check on the gold?
- What? - You know,
- let's see how expensive it is. - Okay, sure.
(The gold bar has been on his mind.)
- This is one of our options. - Option A.
- Okay. - Got it.
(They head to the gold exchange,)
- Do you know where it is? - Yes.
(leaving the duvet behind.)
Hello!
- Thank you, sir. - No problem.
Jong Kook, here are some small ones.
(Eyes widening)
Goodness.
How are gold prices these days?
(Asking the owner)
Prices have gone down a little recently.
(Currently, 3.75g of gold is 700 dollars.)
- Really? - Yes.
- No way. - How much are these keys?
The biggest key is 37.5g.
(37.5g of gold is around 8,000 dollars.)
- I see, 37.5g. - Yes, it weighs about that.
(Interested)
What about that gold bar over there?
- Where is it? - How much are those?
(1kg pure gold bar)
That's over 200,000 dollars.
Is that a kilo of gold?
Why don't we try buying that?
- To see if it gets declined? - I'm sure it will.
If we're thinking about winning, we should buy...
one expensive thing.
I doubt you have anything that costs 100 dollars.
- What? - Maybe 80 to 90 dollars.
(Target price)
The second one from the bottom...
(The owner recommends an item under 100 dollars.)
- is around 0.2g of gold. - It's pretty big.
(0.2g of gold)
- That's nice. It's not that small. - How much is it?
That's 72 dollars.
- That's a decent price. - Right?
- I love it. - I like it too.
Eun Chae seems way more interested than she was in the duvet.
- She... - This is more up her alley.
(Her reaction is quite different from earlier.)
- It's obvious. - Gold is what she likes.
- Right? - I was worried you'd buy the duvet.
- Did that worry you? - She was worried we might buy that.
You should go ahead and tell us that.
(Eun Chae likes gold.)
Eun Chae, take a look at it.
(They take a closer look at the item.)
She's loving this.
- Oh my. - What do you think? Do you like it?
(Loving it)
I'm sorry, but didn't you say you preferred a modern design?
- Look how colorful this is. - Is it the same vibe?
(Embarrassed)
This has a similar vibe to the duvet from earlier.
- I like it. - You seem excited.
- What do you think? - I love it.
(Seeing her reaction, they decided to buy the gold.)
- Shin Bi, do you like it too? - I like it.
- Me too. - It's a little over 70 dollars.
But 70 dollars?
- How much was it again? - Can't we spend close to 100?
Do you have anything that's 100 dollars?
We have something over 100 dollars.
(Employee: "We have something over 100 dollars.")
How much would that be?
The cheapest one you have over 100 dollars.
- That'll be 147 dollars. - Over 140 dollars?
(The cheapest item in the 100-dollar range is 147 dollars.)
- Isn't that too much? - Let's say we bought it.
(147 dollars, 72 dollars)
That'd be a delight to win, but there's...
- a high chance we'll bust. - Totally.
- So for now... - The 70 dollars.
(Should we go all in with 140 dollars?)
Well, 72 dollars is a decent price.
Should we buy this small one or this?
(Or should we play it safe with 70 dollars?)
- The bigger one. - This one.
- How about this one? - This one?
Eun Chae decided for us.
(They choose 72 dollars.)
- Win or lose, let's do it. - Whether we win or lose...
- I doubt the card will be declined. - Of course.
(They decide to play it safe with 72 dollars.)
- There's a greedy look in her eyes. - Okay, let's go with this one.
- Will this... - We're buying this for ourselves.
We don't know if the card will be declined or not.
(It's game over, if the card is declined.)
I have a feeling it won't get declined.
Can you please sign?
(Will they manage to pay for the gold?)
Didn't it go through?
The card was accepted.
(They bought the item.)
(Beaming a smile)
Look at Eun Chae. I haven't seen her...
this happy all day.
Who knew she could smile like that?
Coming on this show was the best choice.
(Delighted)
(While Team Detective manages to buy what they want,)
Let's go inside.
- There's nothing under 100 dollars. - It'll be declined for sure.
(Team Flex arrives at an electronics store.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Do you have anything that's around 110 dollars?
- Wait, 110 dollars? - Yes.
(Team Flex's estimated limit is around the low 100-dollar range.)
- Maybe 120 dollars. - Okay, 120 dollars?
Yes.
- Let's take a look around. - A little over 100 dollars.
We have electric fans in that price range.
(Employee: "We have electric fans in the 100-dollar range.")
- Electric fans? - Yes.
How much is that?
This electric fan is 110 dollars.
- That's perfect. - That's it.
(It's the price they were looking for.)
- This is perfect. - It's exactly 110 dollars.
My guess is the other team will buy something...
- close to 90 dollars. - Right?
(They think Team Detective would've spent about 90 dollars.)
- Yes. - Let's get this for 110 dollars.
What's your take on 110 dollars?
- Let's not leave any regrets. - Let's do this.
No regrets. We're going with 110 dollars.
(It seems everyone agrees.)
- We'll take this. - Sure.
- And now... - Hold on.
- I'd like to say this one thing. - Sure.
I swear I'm not the spy,
but everyone agreeing to 110 dollars is...
Sang Jun, you're not the spy, right?
- I'm not. - That means we're really not it.
I thought it was him,
- but it's not. - It's really not me.
- Then one of you... - What do you mean...
(Bo Hyun suddenly starts rambling.)
- that's why it's not you? - Exactly.
- Where's the logic in that? - How's that logical?
(What's wrong with him?)
- One of you is the spy. - It's not me.
(Excluding Sang Jun and me)
I think 110 dollars is going to be too much.
- You think it's too much? - Yes.
(Bo Hyun's deduction: The spy agreed...)
That's probably why the spy agreed to it.
(since 110 dollars is over the limit.)
- Wait. You're being suspicious. - You're being a bit weird.
- Seriously... - Hold on.
(Is Bo Hyun, who is trying to buy a cheaper item to lose, the spy?)
- Were you in contact with them? - What does that even mean?
Bo Hyun, that was weird for sure.
You think everyone agreed to it too fast.
One of them has to be the spy.
- The spy? - Of course.
- They need to sabotage us. - Right.
(Employee: "Excuse me. Can I recommend something?")
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Can I recommend something?
- What is it? - Yes?
Our wireless earbuds.
- How much is that? - It's 160 dollars.
(He recommends 160-dollar wireless earphones.)
- That won't work. - I'm afraid that's too expensive.
- Sorry about that. - That's too expensive.
(The price is way above the estimated limit of 110 dollars.)
- Wait, 160 dollars? - On our team...
(Tempted)
What if this was a sign?
The employee over there...
- Exactly. - He mentioned 160 dollars.
(Is he a savior who set the perfect price?)
- Wait, 160 dollars? - Maybe it's a sign.
- So I think... - Right? Hear me out.
We're here for "Flex X Cop," and being a tycoon is key.
(Let's go with the more expensive one.)
(As if they were under a spell,)
Why don't we go with this instead?
We were just about to buy the fan...
(they suddenly want to buy a 160-dollar item.)
- when he... - Like it was a sign.
(Tapping)
"How about this?"
Wait. What is it?
Why are you taking him away?
(Flustered)
- Haha, hear me out. - Why on earth...
- We'll hear them anyway. - Why bother taking everyone away?
(They're having an emergency meeting without Jae Seok.)
Jae Seok just upped the price.
- What's the point of this? - I know. He got excited.
It's a bit weird.
Are you seriously whispering while I'm here?
It's just that you suddenly upped the price.
All day,
(Having no trust)
- you've been raising the price. - But I...
- Seok Jin, get over here. - Why?
(Obedient)
Am I with you this time?
- Before I said anything... - He's easily swayed.
Before I said anything, you're the one...
- who said it was a sign. - I said it was a sign.
Come to think of it,
(Intrigued)
- it was him who... - Seok Jin, get over here.
- Sure. - It's like this.
- What you said... - Yes?
- He added to it. - He kept the idea going.
(He keeps changing his mind.)
And he looked happy to do so.
- Hold on. We must duke it out. - Yes.
(Jae Seok wants to take a risk.)
- It's not you, Sang Jun? - It's not me.
If it's not Bo Hyun, it's Jae Seok.
- Why? For real? The spy? - Yes.
(Is Jae Seok, who wants to make a big purchase, the spy?)
- Because it's not us. - The spy?
Who would just go for 160 dollars?
- Listen. - He was too excited.
- If we pay and it goes through, - Yes.
if I were the spy, that means I failed.
- Yes. You can prove it. - Yes.
(If the payment gets declined, he'll be exposed as the spy.)
- If... - What if not?
- If not... - What if not?
- If not... - Then it's Haha.
- It's Haha. - It's me?
(If it doesn't get declined, Haha is likely the spy.)
You want to reduce the amount.
- Him if it fails, him if not. - Yes.
(If it gets declined, Jae Seok is likely the spy.)
- That's it. - Come here, Seok Jin.
- What... - Why?
- I'm confused. - Wait.
It's game over if we can't pay.
I suggest we see what happens.
(Jae Seok wants to give it a try.)
- Yes. I agree. - Let's go for it.
- Let's go. - Okay, deal.
- Okay. - Because...
You're responsible for the outcome.
- Yes. - I have a baseline.
It depends on the outcome.
(They choose the 160-dollar wireless earphones.)
Can you give us one of these?
- I'll swipe the card. - Okay.
- My gosh. - Please.
(He proceeds with the payment.)
- It's 160 dollars. - I'm branded if it doesn't work.
Please go through.
(If the transaction goes through, Haha's the prime suspect.)
- Please. - Please.
- If it doesn't go through... - If it doesn't work...
- Sorry. - We're okay?
(It's a chance to complete the mission and catch the spy.)
- Check the amount. - It's fine.
Can you show us the screen?
(What will happen to Team Flex?)
What's happening?
(10 minutes later)
I had no idea Eun Chae was this talkative.
(Team Flex and Team Detective gathered after the mission.)
Does she talk a lot?
Once we went shopping...
(They come in announcing that she has become Gold Chae.)
She went a bit crazy.
- Did she? - Yes.
They're bringing in the items you bought.
(What kind of item did they choose?)
What is that?
What's that?
Team Detective, show us what you bought.
- Ours? - What's that? It's huge.
(It seems Team Detective purchased many items.)
- Yes. - What is it?
- They bought extra. - One each...
- This one first? - Yes.
I'll reveal it.
- A pillow? - A comforter.
- A comforter. - A comforter.
(A comforter?)
- They bought other stuff? - It's a comforter.
Is it a cooling one?
- Yes. - That's right.
(Cooling summer blanket)
And then...
- What's that? - Gold.
- You bought real gold? - We bought real gold.
For "Flex X Cop"...
(Team Detective's 72-dollar gold purchase went through.)
- She's pleased. - Shall we get something else?
Then we should spend 50 dollars.
(They also bought 50-dollar coins to check the limit.)
I really want this.
It went through.
(The additional 50-dollar transaction was successful.)
- What? - It went through?
Shoot.
(Team Detective figured out that their limit is over 120 dollars.)
I said... We should've spent 70.
We should've bought a 300-dollar bike.
(They think their limit is 300 dollars.)
- A bike? - We're here to keep our word.
(They return to the bedding store.)
- Which design? - I don't care.
The price is what matters.
- The design... - It's fine.
(Their last gamble on the comforter paid off!)
It worked?
Then 300 dollars...
(How much was the comforter?)
- Shoot. - Can't we get this too?
We bought a small gold bar at a reputable gold dealership.
- Isn't it big? - Our team...
(Suddenly getting worried)
Did we spend too little?
- Gosh... - We bought just one item.
- If they see ours... - We got one thing.
Every payment went through?
- What's going on? - How much did they spend?
(How much is the comforter, the most expensive item they got?)
Did we have 1,000 dollars?
Team Flex, what did you buy?
(Team Flex's item to compete against their blanket)
It was more than expected.
What did you get?
(Wireless earphones)
- What's that? - Galaxy Buds?
- Yes. - For how much?
- They're expensive. - How much are they?
- They're expensive. - Aren't they 200 dollars?
They're Galaxy Buds?
What's happening?
(Team Flex bought the 160-dollar earphones.)
It went through.
- That's... - Okay. You have my support.
- You're safe. - See?
- Okay. - We must play big.
(Thanks to Jae Seok, the 160-dollar payment went through.)
If it was 80 dollars... Should we have spent more?
(They made a big purchase, but Team Detective got them worried.)
- Gosh. - They bought a lot.
- No way. - They're good.
- Something expensive... - I was surprised.
- It kept working. - I'll announce the total.
(Team Detective: ? dollars, Team Flex: 160 dollars)
That looks expensive.
(The amount Team Flex spent is revealed first.)
- The amount... - Please.
- Team Flex spent. - We spent less.
(Their most expensive item is 160 dollars.)
- It's 160 dollars. - Yes.
(Dismayed exclamation)
(Why do they look devastated?)
The most expensive item Team Detective bought...
(Team Detective's biggest amount is...)
was the 150-dollar comforter.
(150 dollars.)
- What? - What about the gold?
The 150-dollar comforter.
Team Flex won.
- What was this? - The gold.
- It was cheaper. - I see.
(Their blanket is 150 dollars.)
We bought this and it went through.
We got this just for the heck of it.
(They bought multiple cheap items.)
- Then... - We won?
- Yes. - Okay!
(Team Flex won by just ten dollars.)
Team Flex won...
- by just ten dollars. - How much did the cards have?
We gave you 300 dollars each.
- Then... - We spent 297 dollars.
(Gold card: 72 dollars, cold coins: 50 dollars)
(Team Detective's Transaction Details: Total 297 dollars)
You got really close.
(They maxed out the limit.)
- We could've gone bust. - We spent 297 dollars.
We didn't because we got this.
I should've gotten a bike.
That was so close.
- Ten dollars. - A ten-dollar difference.
It doesn't matter. We're sharing the hint anyway.
- Yes. We shared ours. - It depends.
We'll see first.
(Team Flex, the winning team, gets a hint.)
- Should we share? - Can't we?
- Should we? - It's fine.
Okay, then.
Team Flex won, and you can choose between a hint...
on how to disarm the bomb or the undercover detective.
- The detective. - Yes, the spy.
- The spy. - Let's identify them.
- That's only right. - That's the right play.
(They pick a hint on the undercover detective to catch the spy.)
- Yes. - That's right.
- The spy hint. - Yes.
What does it say?
(The undercover detective is over 170cm tall.)
Hey. Then it's not Haha?
- Hey, you. - That's...
(To the staff members)
You lot are really mean and cruel.
Include me! Suspect me.
Don't rile me up. Don't do that.
(Approaching)
Don't do that. It's not like that.
(What kind of hint is it?)
- Why is he annoyed? - What's wrong?
- Is that right? - That includes me too.
Yes. It's just Ji Hyo.
I'm 171.5cm tall.
- Include me. - But based on the hint,
we can exclude two.
(Only Ji Hyo and Haha are excluded.)
No, that includes me.
- How tall are you? - I'm 171cm.
(Haha would rather be on the suspect list.)
He's in.
- But... - Count me in.
- The hint... - Is he included?
Oh, is that the hint? That he's under 170cm?
No!
That's it.
(Detective Kim quickly figured out the clue as Haha was freaking out.)
- No. - Oh, dear. You're out.
- Not me. - It's not you or Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo and Haha are off their radar.)
- Haha's out. - No, I'm...
How tall are you, Haha?
I'm 171.5cm.
You're 162.7cm.
No, that's Shorry's height.
(Haha was ruled out as the spy because of his physical condition.)
You're 168cm.
- No. I'm 171.5cm. - Or 167.5cm.
Ji Hyo's definitely out.
It's time for the chairman to launder the money.
This is their last opportunity.
The last race is the tycoons versus the detectives.
(Team Flex: Tycoons and an undercover detective)
We hid hints about the chairman, the undercover detective,
(Team Detective: Detectives and an undercover secretary)
the undercover secretary, and handcuffs.
(The hints are scattered inside this building!)
- Handcuffs? - Handcuffs.
We must find them one by one.
(The hints are inside the blue envelopes.)
(And there are handcuffs.)
We must handcuff them.
Team Detective can apprehend the chairman once everyone...
has a pair of handcuffs.
The undercover detective must also find a pair.
The undercover detective and all of us need handcuffs?
Yes.
We must find the handcuffs first, then.
Team Flex must disarm all the bombs tied to the briefcase.
- That's the hard part. - You win if everyone...
excluding the undercover detective can escape.
If the undercover detective manages to escape with you,
or if Team Detective apprehends the chairman before you escape,
Team Detective wins.
You can rip off name tags during the race.
(Yu Jae Seok)
That activates the temporary pause.
The person whose name tag gets ripped off must stand still...
- in silence for three minutes. - Okay.
- They don't die. - No.
We'll take you to your starting positions.
(Everyone moves to their designated starting spots.)
She's lying down?
Race, start.
(Se Chan starts searching.)
Anyone who acts strangely today.
If any two stand to talk, that will look suspicious.
Okay, Se Chan, not bad.
I'm the first to find a hint.
(Animated sound effects)
(Se Chan found the first hint.)
"This person isn't the chairman?"
(Someone's photo was turned into a drawing.)
Who is this person? Who is this?
Is this a magic eye thing? Who is this?
Doesn't it feel like there's something in this room?
See, Se Chan? My gosh.
(Se Chan found another hint.)
How refreshing.
Ever seen this before? Here's one more.
(His 3rd hint already)
The hints... Another one? Why am I so good today?
(Running Man's Indiana Jones found 4 already.)
How refreshing.
It's not Sang Jun.
"This isn't the chairman's first visit to Running Man."
It's not their first visit?
(It's the first visit for just Sang Jun on that team.)
It's not Sang Jun.
"The chairman has released a song."
Sang Jun hasn't released a song.
(This hint excludes Deep Black.)
(What's the last hint?)
The hints...
To be honest, they both mean the same thing.
(It also excludes Sang Jun.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok found a hint.)
- I found one. - Me too. There's one.
(Flailing her arms)
Let me get it. No, let's share.
(The hint is here.)
(Promise)
- Okay. - Let's share.
- Ye Eun. - Let me try.
Aren't I taller, though?
(Ripping off)
- What was that? - Ye Eun, freeze for three minutes.
- Why me? - You can't speak, either.
(Lose name tag and freeze for 3 minutes in silence)
Stay here for three minutes. This hint...
Excuse me, Chan Hee.
(Snorty giggles)
(Jae Seok silences Ye Eun and steals the hint.)
This isn't the chairman's first visit to the show.
That means Sang Jun isn't the chairman.
(As everyone has guessed, Sang Jun isn't the chairman!)
This isn't the chairman's first visit.
(This isn't the chairman's first visit to Running Man.)
I had to stay silent and still for three minutes...
(Ye Eun bumps into Se Chan after being released.)
because someone ripped off my name tag.
- Who ripped off your name tag? - Jae Seok did.
- Why? - He did it out of the blue.
How did you find so many hints?
Give me some information.
- Look over there. - Okay.
Gosh, what's wrong with you?
(He tried to eliminate her.)
What on earth is wrong with you?
Are you crazy?
I'll make you stay still for three minutes...
so that you'll stop nagging at me.
What's wrong with this jerk?
Listen carefully. Jong Kook is dangerous.
Why?
Jong Kook!
(Tiger happens to be watching.)
He tried to rip off my name tag.
For goodness' sake.
I didn't want to hear her voice.
(A valid reason)
- To be honest, it's meaningless. - I know.
- She... I know. - It's just a three-minute break.
- But... - It doesn't eliminate you.
- But he won't show me the hints. - Hey.
- Did you find the hints? - Yes.
He found so many hints,
- so he should share them. - You should share the hints.
I can't do that. Do you know why?
- We're a team. - The undercover secretary...
(The spy might leak information.)
- might leak information. - I'm not it.
- Right? These hints... - This jerk is suspicious.
This jerk is suspicious.
(Ye Eun has to freeze for 3 minutes again.)
- What's wrong with this jerk? - Stop talking.
Silence!
(What Se Chan says makes sense, but his behavior is suspicious.)
Ye Eun, three minutes.
- He is so annoying. - Silence!
- Jong Kook. - Yes.
- He is acting strange - He is acting strange indeed.
He won't share the hints.
But he has always acted strange.
(Is the suspicious Se Chan the chairman's secretary?)
You startled me. Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok on Team Flex approaches him.)
- Se Chan, what did you find? - I found many hints, but...
How did you find so many hints?
I'm good at finding hints.
How...
Se Chan found all of them.
What's up with him?
(Proud)
I found two hints on each floor.
You took all the hints.
(Bo Hyun on Team Flex also joins them.)
It's important to be faster than the others.
Why did you take so many hints?
I can't share these hints.
Why... Are you going to rip off my name tag?
(Ripping off)
(Se Chan has to pause for 3 minutes.)
Stay still.
- Is this allowed? - Se Chan,
(Stealing)
pause for three minutes.
Jae Seok, is it okay to steal the hints?
Of course, it's okay.
Of course. Please put it back.
(Ripping off)
My goodness.
(What?)
He took all of my hints.
(Bo Hyun steals the hints by ripping off Jae Seok's name tag.)
- I mean... - Jae Seok, pause for three minutes.
(Jae Seok also has to pause for 3 minutes.)
Se Chan.
This is ridiculous. Jae Seok.
(He lost everything.)
So that was a waste of time.
(Bo Hyun must be a spy.)
He must be a spy.
(He checks his spoils.)
This isn't the chairman's first visit.
(Is Bo Hyun really a spy?)
In that case...
(Meanwhile, Eun Chae is searching.)
Here it is.
(She finds a hint.)
Hold on.
(She searches the artificial plants.)
(She even acquires handcuffs!)
(Meanwhile, Bo Hyun's victims)
(They finally become free.)
Jae Seok.
- You know... - Had you been discreet,
(Give me the mask.)
I would've shared the hints with you.
We can't share the hints since we're in different teams.
(The mask, please.)
- Are you mixing up the masks? - No, we aren't.
- I'll carry mine around. - Give me mine.
(In a rush)
- I'll carry it. - I'll carry mine around.
There must be someone who didn't brush their teeth.
(They're worried about getting someone's mask.)
There is that issue.
Hey, Bo Hyun! I'll find him.
I can't believe Bo Hyun.
I can't believe him.
That isn't Bo Hyun.
- No, that's Sang Jun. - Sang Jun.
(Sang Jun on Team Flex shows up.)
- Sang Jun. - Yes?
- You... - Sang Jun.
I'm not a spy.
What is it? What did you find?
- But... - What?
What are you doing?
- You aren't on our team. - Why do you ask?
(We're on different teams.)
- Why do you ask? - You aren't on our team.
- You asked me so naturally. - You aren't on our team.
- You need to team up with me. - Why?
Because I trust you.
What? What are you talking about?
- Are you a spy? - Why are you stirring up trouble?
You need to trust me.
(Detective Yang drops a cryptic remark.)
- Sang Jun, you need to trust me. - Sang Jun, let's see it.
- Hold on. - That's right. That's it.
(Deep Black is confused.)
- Come here. - It isn't like that.
- Why... - Is he crazy?
What were the two of you doing?
- No. - Jae Seok.
- Hey. - Bo Hyun ripped off my name tag...
- and took my hints. - Jae Seok.
- He ripped off your name tag? - Let's do that later.
(Discreet)
What are you talking about?
Bo Hyun ripped off my name tag, so Se Chan and I stayed together.
(Bo Hyun ripped off my name tag, so Se Chan and I stayed together.)
I can't trust you.
(Sang Jun is suspicious of Jae Seok who was with Se Chan.)
How am I supposed to trust you?
- This is so frustrating. - I can't show you the hint.
(Going up)
- You... - We're on the same team.
- Jae Seok. - Okay. In that case...
Come to the third floor later.
I can't believe him.
(Ssaebssaeb shakes up the tycoons.)
Then I'll go...
and check the story with Bo Hyun.
Bo Hyun ripped off my name tag...
(This is the truth.)
and took my hints.
(Not believing him)
Stay there for a second.
- I'll go and check. - This is driving me crazy.
(He keeps saying he'll check.)
(Thus, distrust sprouts amidst Team Flex members.)
(Team Detective members gather around.)
- Did you find something? - Yes.
I'll show you.
(Eun Chae shares the hint.)
(This isn't the chairman's first visit to Running Man.)
Did you see it?
Hold on. Judging by the way she shared the hint with us,
(She can't be the spy.)
- she can't be the secretary. - I know.
- Right? - Se Chan suddenly said this...
- to me. - Se Chan...
"Hey, Jong Kook is suspicious."
- He said that downstairs. - Hey.
- It must be Se Chan. - I was like, "Why?"
"I'm telling you that he is suspicious."
Listen carefully. Jong Kook is dangerous.
- I was like, "Why?" - Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious!
- Check the cameras. - Nothing happened between us.
I found it strange, so I asked him to show me the hints.
(Ye Eun's deduction: Se Chan, who suspected Jong Kook...)
But he ripped off my name tag.
(and ripped off my name tag, is the spy.)
- Se Chan ripped off my name tag. - What?
(Is Se Chan really the spy as they think?)
- It's Se Chan. I'm sure of it. - It's Se Chan. It has to be him.
- There he is! - Jong Kook.
(The spy is here!)
- The secretary is here! - He is the secretary.
- The secretary is here! - I'm not the secretary.
- Se Chan, where are the hints? - Jong Kook,
(Se Chan, the prime suspect for being the spy, appears.)
- Come here. - I got all of my six hints stolen.
- Come here. Hey. - I got all of them stolen.
- How did you get them stolen? - You...
- You didn't show me the hints. - You said that I was suspicious.
Says who?
(Witness)
I told him.
I say that about everyone.
- I say that about everyone. - Hey.
He is suspicious. He must be the secretary.
- He is suspicious indeed. - He is the secretary.
Did you let them it off?
- Did you let them it off? - Who?
(Eun Chae strongly suspects him.)
- No way. - Seriously.
- Who ripped off your name tag? - Bo Hyun.
(He starts putting pressure on him.)
No, Jae Seok ripped off my name tag.
Listen. Jae Seok ripped off my name tag.
Then Bo Hyun ripped off Jae Seok's name tag right away.
Then who took your hints?
(Then who took your hints?)
Bo Hyun.
- Bo Hyun is the chairman... - That's right.
- and he is the secretary. - Jae Seok... Okay.
(Is Se Chan, who gave information to the other chairman, the spy?)
- Who? - So he had the hints...
He had the hints in his hand.
- What a wild claim. - He held them up like this.
He let his name tag get ripped off and went, "What?"
(Deducting)
Then Bo Hyun took the hints and got rid of them.
"Chairman, hurry up and rip off my name tag!"
(I'm sure it went like this.)
You're wrong.
- I can't believe it. - He is the secretary.
(Is Bo Hyun the chairman of Team Flex?)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok finds a hint.)
(And Bo Hyun runs somewhere.)
(Who entered the chairman's hideout, bomb room?)
For goodness' sake.
(Haha?)
(Which hint did Jae Seok find just now?)
(The chairman's wife is a singer.)
That means the chairman is Haha.
Haha, you're the chairman in Team Flex...
(30 minutes before the opening scene)
whose identity is a secret.
(Haha is the chairman.)
That sounds cool.
(During the money laundering time before lunch,)
Are you filming me?
(everyone was blindfolded.)
(The chairman entered the bomb room.)
Here it is.
The bomb that's attached to the money briefcase...
(A challenge to get the money briefcase)
has seven wires.
(Cut the 5 correct wires out of 7 to defuse the bomb.)
Among them, five wires defuse the bomb...
and two wires detonate the bomb.
(Cutting the wrong wire will set off the bomb.)
If the bomb gets detonated, is the game over?
If the bomb gets detonated,
(If the bomb goes off, a hint about the chairman will be revealed.)
Team Detective will receive a hint on the chairman.
So you must choose the wires carefully.
Before you attempt to defuse the bomb,
- we'll give you a quiz. - What?
If you answer correctly,
we'll tell you one defusing wire.
I'll test my luck.
(It hurts my pride.)
Why would you give me a quiz?
Don't be so rude to the chairman.
You have had this quiz before. You might remember the answer.
(But he has had this quiz before.)
Here comes the question.
(The question is revealed.)
Inside the Seokgatap Pagoda of Bulguksa Temple in Gyeongju,
this scroll of printed text was discovered.
What's the name of the oldest surviving...
woodblock-printed text in the world?
It's the oldest surviving woodblock-printed text...
(In summer 3 years ago, at the Bulguksa Temple,)
in the world.
- The Great Dharani Sutra. - The Great Dharani Sutra.
(Haha got the correct answer!)
(The Great Dharani Sutra)
Ji...
Jikji...
(Incorrect)
Incorrect. The answer is...
(The Great Dharani Sutra, the world's first woodblock print)
the Great Dharani Sutra.
(Jikji, the world's first book printed with movable metal type)
Please cut 1 of the 7 wires.
(He got the answer wrong, so he has to defuse the bomb without a hint.)
The red one.
One.
(He chooses number 1, the red wire.)
Two.
Three.
(Success)
You've succeeded in cutting a defusing wire.
(He has found 1 of the 5 correct wires!)
- See you next time. - Okay.
Just now,
the chairman has succeeded in removing one defusing wire...
(The news was announced that 1 defusing wire had been removed.)
for the bomb.
(Current time)
You cut a wire a moment ago.
(As time passed, 5 more wires were added.)
- Five wires have been added. - Okay.
So you must cut 5 correct wires among the total of 12.
(He needs to find 4 more correct wires.)
Here comes the question.
(A quiz for the correct wire)
Who is the author of "Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind,"
a worldwide best-seller...
about the history of humankind?
- Didn't I give this question? - That's right.
Who wrote it?
(Last month)
("Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind")
A foreigner did.
A foreigner wrote it.
Who is the author?
Homo Sapiens.
"Homo?"
(Answer: Yuval Harari)
I gave this question!
Homo... Homo Pitertotacrokus.
(Incorrect)
Werber Sobert? It was something like that.
- Incorrect. - Who is the author?
(He got this question wrong too!)
- Yuval Harari. - For goodness' sake.
(He should pick a wire without a hint again!)
I remember now.
Now, please choose a wire.
(There are only 4 correct wires among the remaining 11!)
(The chairman chooses blindly after failing to answer correctly.)
I made up my mind.
(He chooses number 3, the green wire.)
(The bomb didn't go off.)
You cut the correct one.
(Luckily, number 3 was also correct!)
You can try again.
But if I fail...
But if I don't do it...
I'll choose one more.
Here comes the next question.
- What's the full name... - For goodness' sake.
of the composer, Mozart?
Amadeus...
Mozart.
The full name.
Amadeus Mozart.
- Incorrect. - What?
- Wolfgang. - Wolf...
(The full name is Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart.)
I'm sorry.
(He failed to answer correctly for the third time!)
I was so close.
(He must cut another wire without a hint!)
All right.
I need to hurry up.
(Chairman Ha is on pins and needles.)
They're suspicious.
They're nearly certain that I'm the chairman.
It's strange.
(He blindly chooses number 6, the yellow wire.)
(Will he get lucky and survive this time as well?)
One, two...
Hold on. In that case...
(Meanwhile, Team Detective members are together.)
- The chairman... - Let's go and find him.
Since the chairman detonated the bomb,
we'll give you a hint on his identity.
- Give us the hint. Let's hear it. - Okay.
Two, three.
(Chairman Ha cut the wrong wire.)
The chairman must've cut the wrong wire.
When Jong Kook lost a point during the jokgu mission,
- the chairman laughed at him. - Come on.
- It's Haha. - It's too easy.
- Haha laughed at me loudly. - But everyone laughed at you.
- I'm serious. - Come here.
- But... - Everyone laughed at you.
- Haha... - Jae Seok laughed at you loudly.
(Correct)
Haha was especially loud.
- No. It was Jae Seok. - I saw...
Seok Jin laugh at you.
(When Jong Kook failed to head the ball)
That's it!
(Will they remember that Chairman Haha laughed loudly?)
It could be Haha.
(Correct)
I don't think it's Haha.
You think that way...
(Team Detective gets closer to discovering Chairman Ha's identity.)
because you look down on Haha.
- Me? - Yes.
Jong Kook is dangerous. It's in his tone.
- Who? - Don't you agree?
(And Se Chan suspects Jong Kook of being a spy.)
- He keeps framing me. - He does.
- He keeps framing me, right? - Yes.
- What? - Se Chan is the spy.
(On the contrary, Jong Kook is suspicious of Se Chan.)
- That's why... - Se Chan is the spy. I'm certain.
- he let them take the hints. - He did that.
- That's the reason why. - He didn't show me the hints.
He let them take the hints. I'm sure of it.
(Se Chan searches other places.)
Is this really a lecture room of Chung-Ang University?
Yes.
Had I been a good student, I would've sat here.
Shall I listen to the lecture?
So this is how it looks.
Do they take roll calls?
(Professor)
- Yang Se Chan. - Yes?
I'm Yang Se Chan and I entered in 2005.
(Laughing)
(Somewhere in a parallel universe,)
Like that?
- Yes. - All right.
(he entered Chung-Ang University in 2005.)
Yes, I'm here.
So that's how it goes. Does the professor stand there?
(Detailed imagination)
(My goodness)
It would've been cool.
After the lecture, you take your books and leave.
Hey. See you at the library later.
(Laughing)
Give me a break.
(Startled)
(Detective Kim was listening to everything.)
- Give me a break. - Have you gone to a university?
- Seriously. - I entered Chung-Ang University...
(The Chung-Ang University student is blushing.)
- in 2005. - For goodness' sake.
Hey. For goodness' sake.
(No hint?)
- Are there no hints? - No.
You weren't even looking for them. You're suspicious.
- What do you mean? - You're suspicious.
(They're suspicious of each other.)
- Jong Kook. - Se Chan.
I need to find the handcuffs.
(Is there the undercover secretary among the two of them?)
Okay.
This is driving me crazy.
Hold on a second.
(Meanwhile, Chairman Ha who detonated the bomb)
I'll bring Jae Seok to get the questions right.
That means the chairman is Haha.
(Thanks to a hint, Jae Seok learns about Haha's identity.)
(And Haha begins to look for Jae Seok.)
Where is he?
- Yes. - What?
- Jae Seok. - Where is Jae Seok?
(He meets the rest of Team Flex.)
- What? - Did you find many hints?
I heard that you ripped off Jae Seok's name tag...
(He checks the facts like a broken record.)
and stole the hints.
Really?
(All the tycoons learn about Bo Hyun's name tag fiasco!)
- It must be true! - As for that...
It must be true!
(Fact checked)
- As for that... - How could you do that?
(He suddenly becomes the prime suspect.)
- It wasn't my intention. - How could you do that?
My goodness.
- I mean... - I got goosebumps.
- Bo Hyun, is it true? - It's him.
- Listen to me. - Is it true?
(Jumping)
It's true. But let me explain.
(He hurriedly defends himself.)
Jae Seok ripped off Se Chan's name tag...
and took his hints.
He didn't want to share the hints, so I took off his name tag.
(The hint)
(The undercover detective)
- I'm not the spy. - He must've done that...
(Suspicious)
because he is on the same team...
- as Se Chan. - What?
(Is he the victimized tycoon or the undercover detective?)
I'm not the spy.
Hold on a second.
- Jae Seok. - Did he rip off your name tag?
(Jae Seok knows about Chairman Ha's identity.)
Did Bo Hyun rip off your name tag?
Yes, he did.
- I did that because you... - Jae Seok.
(He finally meets Jae Seok, the brainy member!)
How did it...
Is it true?
(But they can't talk freely since the undercover detective is here.)
Right now...
- What? - You tried to hoard the hints.
Jae Seok, we need to talk.
(Secretive)
(Chairman Ha requests to talk with Jae Seok alone.)
- We need to talk. - What?
Hold on.
- What is it? - I...
I'm the chairman.
- That's right. - So now,
we need to escape.
I'm certain that you aren't the spy...
because you shared the hints with me.
(Haha's deduction: Jae Seok isn't a spy because he shared...)
- That's right. - You also found...
(an important with him and helped him succeed his mission.)
- It's Bo Hyun. - I'm completely certain.
Bo Hyun is the spy.
- I told you that repeatedly. - Bo Hyun is the spy.
(Chairman Ha brings Jae Seok to the bomb room.)
- Hurry up. - What do we need to do to escape?
I'll tell you.
What do we need to do to escape?
I need to answer the questions correctly...
To cut the wires?
- To cut the wires. - What kind of questions?
- They're so hard. - What kind of questions?
Who wrote "Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind?"
(Correct)
- Yuval Harari. - That's right. I got it wrong.
- And... Was it Dabotap Pagoda? - For goodness' sake.
The first book that was found inside the pagoda.
(Clapping)
- Okay. The Great Dharani Sutra. - That's right. I got it wrong.
(Correct)
- Gosh, you guys made him... - What was the other one?
(Correct again)
- the chairman on purpose. - What was the other one?
(He is a lot worse than expected.)
There was another one I got wrong. In any case, follow me.
Which way is it?
Be quiet.
(Chairman Ha gets himself a trustworthy helper.)
- Is this the place? - Here.
(He takes the smart one to the bomb room.)
Jae Seok, hurry up.
All right.
(Desperate)
We'll answer the questions.
Please answer them.
You cut the wrong wire before.
Because of that, five wires have been added.
(With the failure earlier, 5 wires have been added,)
(so there are 17 wires now.)
Okay.
(Cut off 3 correct wires to defuse the bomb!)
- Can we answer right away? - Yes.
- Yes. - Here comes the question.
A legal way of delaying...
a legislative business...
- at the Congress... - Filibuster.
Correct.
(He answers it correctly before hearing the whole question.)
That's it. Please get one more question right.
Please cut wire number ten.
(Since he answered it correctly, he gets to cut the correct Wire 10.)
- Number ten. - How many wires need to be cut?
Three remain.
Really?
(Now, 2 correct wires remain.)
I did it.
- We'll answer one more question. - If we do this...
(Immediately going for the next quiz)
- Here comes the next question. - Okay.
- If I know, I'll answer. - You can do that.
Look at me when you ask the question.
What's the name of the book in the left hand...
of the statue of Sejong the Great in Gwanghwamun?
(He gives up immediately.)
You should answer it.
Isn't it too easy?
Is there a book in Sejong the Great's left hand?
(He is clearly holding a book.)
- I thought it was the right hand. - It has been asked on the show.
- Is that so? - It has six syllables.
- "Hunminjeongeum Haerye." - Correct.
"Hunminjeongeum Haerye."
Correct.
(Jae Seok answers instead of Chairman Ha again.)
He did it.
"Hunminjeongeum Haerye."
- Please cut wire number 4. - Cut wire number 4.
(This time, he removes Wire 4.)
If we cut one more wire...
Number four.
(Only 1 correct wire remains!)
(If they cut 1 more correct wire, they'll defuse the bomb!)
I'll answer the next one.
It could be Seok Jin or...
(Meanwhile...)
(Team Detective still doesn't know about Chairman Ha.)
It could be Seok Jin or...
Haha.
(The chairman)
I don't think it's Haha.
- I think it's Seok Jin. - I mean...
(The chairman)
- Seok Jin? - Yes.
- Seok Jin does seem like it. - Yes.
(Suspicious)
- Look at him. He is so busy. - Yes, he is busy.
(Tycoon Seok Sam runs around diligently.)
Over there.
- Jong Kook. - Yes, Seok Jin?
"Jong Kook" sounded strange. Hold on a second.
- Seok Jin. - Am I very suspicious?
You approached me and pretended to open the door.
(Ji Seok Sam was busy running around even as he was suspected.)
- No. - Okay. I got it.
(Making it obvious)
I'll go downstairs.
He didn't have to say it out loud. "I'll go downstairs."
(Strange)
I need to hurry.
(Even now, he runs around.)
- I need to hurry. - Seok Jin.
Why did you cut the wrong wire?
(Sounding him out)
- Listen. - What?
We don't have much time. I'll take the risk.
What?
Jong Kook, come here for a second. I'll take the risk.
- What? - He is suspicious, right?
(He says he'll take the risk and calls over Kim Muscles.)
- He is definitely suspicious. - Yes.
- I'll take the risk. - What?
(What kind of risk is Seok Sam talking about?)
- What do you mean? What risk? - Jong Kook, come here.
- Jong Kook, come alone. - Me? Why me?
- Come on. - Why me?
(Very serious)
- Why? Seok Jin. - What risk?
- Jong Kook. - Seok Jin.
- I'll take the leap of faith. - What do you mean?
- I'll take the leap of faith. - Okay.
I know who the chairman is.
Did you figure it out?
- I know who the chairman is. - Did you figure it out?
(Why is he sharing the chairman's information with Team Detective?)
- Who is it? - Haha.
- Haha. - I knew it!
(That means...)
- Who is it? I knew it! - Haha.
Seok Jin, are you the undercover detective?
- Yes. - Okay.
- I was right. It's Haha. - Hey.
(Seok Sam is the undercover detective.)
Hurry up.
- Today, you're... - Okay.
(Team Detective's undercover detective...)
the undercover detective that infiltrated...
(who infiltrated Team Flex)
- Team Flex. - The undercover detective.
(Undercover Detective, Jee Seok Jin)
The day has finally come.
Today is the day.
- Rewind the camera. - He kicked it.
(You lose a point for saying "camera.")
You lose a point for saying "camera."
(Undercover detective messed up purposefully to set Team Flex back.)
- Darn you. - Out you go.
- Good job! - Sorry.
The chairman will escape, right?
How will he escape?
He can open the door and jump out now.
(He even asked the method of escape.)
(After Haha failed to defuse the bomb,)
The chairman laughed at him.
(the hint was shared with the undercover detective as well.)
That doesn't help at all. Everyone laughed at him.
(Chairman hint: When Jong Kook lost a point...)
Wait.
(during the jokgu mission, the chairman laughed at him.)
I remember it clearly.
I know who laughed at him the loudest.
I thought of Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo used to laugh like that whenever Jong Kook failed.
(Laughing)
Ha!
I thought his laugh sounded similar.
(Someone reminded him of Kwang Soo who always laughed at Jong Kook.)
Do you know who gave me that impression?
Haha.
(He figured out the chairman's identity!)
Haha gave me that impression.
The chairman is...
Haha.
We don't have much time. I'll take the risk.
What?
(The undercover detective took the risk with Detective Kook.)
Jong Kook, come here for a second. I'll take the risk.
- Who is it? - Haha.
- Haha. - I knew it!
(Thus, Team Detective figured out Chairman Ha's identity.)
Seok Jin, are you the undercover detective?
- Yes. - Okay.
- I was right. It's Haha. - Hey.
What now? We need to hurry up and find the handcuffs.
(All Team Detective members, including the undercover detective,)
- We need to hurry up. - The handcuffs.
I'll stay with the others downstairs.
(must find the handcuffs and arrest the chairman.)
Shin Bi.
It's Haha.
(He tells Shin Bi about Chairman Ha's identity.)
- Why? - It's Haha.
It's Haha.
- Hurry up and find the handcuffs. - The first floor.
(They need to find the handcuffs before Team Flex escapes.)
Hey, hurry up and find them.
- It's Haha. - Really?
(Accepting it immediately)
- Jong Kook, you're so smart. - It's Haha.
(Shin Bi finds the handcuffs.)
(Team Detective currently has 2 sets of handcuffs.)
If we cut one more wire...
(At that time, Chairman Ha is about to defuse the last bomb.)
- We just need to get everyone. - That's right.
I'll answer the next one.
This one hasn't been asked before.
(Writer)
- Here comes the question. - Okay.
Why are you looking at Jae Seok?
(Upset)
- Look at Haha. - I'll answer it.
What's the name of the Roman emperor...
that later came to mean "Emperor?"
(I don't know.)
Go ahead and answer it.
- Emperor? - Kaiser.
- Kaiser. - Kaiser.
Your answer is correct.
Yes! I got half of the answers right.
(Correct)
(Jae Seok answers the final quiz without fail.)
- Kaiser. - Kaiser.
- Cut number 9. - Number 9?
We got it now.
(He cuts off Wire 9, the final real bomb wire.)
We're going to get rich now!
(The bomb is defused.)
- Did it work? - The bomb has been defused.
I'll tell you the passcode.
It's 720814.
(The briefcase's passcode is 720814.)
Should I open it?
Isn't that my birthday?
- What? - He...
- I'm the chairman. - He's the chairman.
(Dissatisfied)
Did you assume I'll be the one answering the questions?
(Still, only the chairman can open the money briefcase.)
Seven, two...
- Seven, two. - Two.
Zero, eight, one, four.
(Opening the briefcase)
(They get cash and a car key.)
There's a car as well!
We're leaving in this car.
(Immersed)
Hold on. Where's the car?
You have to find the car.
(For Team Flex to win, he must find the car and leave with the tycoons.)
You have to get all your team members in the car and leave.
(But they lose if they bring the undercover detective with them.)
I'll get in the car and start the engine.
(That's ridiculous.)
- You can bring everyone to the car. - What?
(He wants to leave all the work to Jae Seok until the end.)
- The answers were... - You...
- So you... - The chairman...
- What do you actually do? - I'm the chairman.
I'm the chairman!
(The figurehead chairman abuses his title.)
You're only a tycoon. You should serve the chairman.
(Regardless, Jae Seok must take him to escape.)
Goodness. Hold on, then the car...
Then I should bring everyone except Bo Hyun.
(They still suspect Bo Hyun of being the undercover detective.)
- Why did Bo Hyun rip off yours? - Exactly.
Bo Hyun made a suggestion when he got in the van.
(If they run away with Seok Sam, Team Flex loses.)
Does that even make sense?
- Let's first head out. - The spy was right there.
Let's first go out.
What should I do? What should I do with this, Jae Seok?
(The money briefcase is too noticeable.)
Where should I hide it?
Put it behind there.
(He hides it out of sight.)
Okay.
(Jae Seok heads out to gather the tycoons.)
Who could the spy be?
Jae Seok!
(He encounters the fake tycoon.)
Seok Sam.
Jae Seok. Stay there.
Stay there, Jae Seok.
(Acting)
Who's the spy?
I don't know who the spy is.
Isn't it Bo Hyun?
- Aren't you the spy? - Come on. It's not me.
- Aren't you the chairman? - I'm not.
- The chairman... - Seok Jin.
Why are you so curious about who the chairman is?
(Suspicious)
(Feeling guilty)
Don't try to make me the spy. It's not me.
I'm not trying to make you the spy.
You've been looking for the chairman this whole time.
- The chairman... - We should be looking...
- for the spy. - That's Bo Hyun.
Bo Hyun is the spy. Trust me.
(Confused)
I'm telling you. It's Bo Hyun.
(To the detectives)
- Quickly find the handcuffs! - What?
- Quickly find the handcuffs! - Yes?
(Halts)
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
Did you just say "yes?"
(Feigning ignorance)
- What? - You...
(The undercover detective unconsciously answered Jong Kook.)
He told you to look for the handcuffs and you said "yes."
- Hey... - Don't keep accusing me.
(Sweating)
But...
Don't make me look like the spy.
(Please)
He told you to look for the handcuffs and you said "yes."
- I was just reacting. - I mean...
- Why... - He's trying to pin it on me.
(Seok Sam had been hiding well. Will he be discovered now?)
- I'm not. You're... - It's not me.
(Meanwhile, Chairman Ha searches the parking lot.)
Is it a Carnival?
(Beep)
It's over there.
(Chairman Ha finds the getaway car.)
Okay.
The car is here.
(Now he needs to get the briefcase and the tycoons in the car.)
(But first, he needs to identify the undercover detective.)
I'll first put the briefcase in the car and lock it.
Jae Seok!
Haha.
(He ignores Bo Hyun's urgent shouts.)
- Hold on, Bo Hyun. - Haha!
See me first. I know why you think it's me.
- I... - Why did you rip the name tag?
(The name tag)
- I know why you think it's me. - Okay.
I know what you are.
- What? - You're the chairman.
Why do you think it's me?
(He knows Haha's identity!)
(Lone wolf Bo Hyun found a crucial hint.)
(The chairman's wife is a celebrity.)
It's Haha.
(Candidates: Yu Jae Seok, Haha, Kang Sang Jun)
(Chairman hint)
It's Haha. It's definitely him.
(He is sure that Haha is the chairman.)
There's no one but Haha.
You're the chairman.
(Lying)
I'm not.
- Even now... - Seriously.
(He is sure that Bo Hyun is the undercover detective.)
What are you basing that on?
(Upset)
He's denying it to the very end.
(The real tycoon is excluded until the end.)
Seriously.
Hold on. Come with me.
- Haha! - Stay there for a bit, Bo Hyun.
(Feeling lonely)
Come on.
- Give me the car key. - I found it.
(He shares the car location, keeping it a secret from Bo Hyun.)
- You did? Where is it? - It's outside.
Go that way...
You'll find the car.
(For Team Flex to win, Bo Hyun needs to get in the car.)
I'll take the briefcase there.
- Okay. - Bo Hyun...
Honestly, you can't blame us for suspecting you.
- You agree there, right? - But...
why are you lying?
I didn't lie.
Could I talk to you for a moment, Sang Jun?
(This time, he excludes Bo Hyun and calls Sang Jun.)
Don't regret later. I've put everything on the line.
Regret what? Why are you threatening me?
- It's scary. - It really isn't me.
Why are you being so scary? "Don't regret later?"
(Will victory slip further away from Team Flex like this?)
If you say that...
I received the car key...
- and found the car as well. - Okay.
(He shares the information about the car to Sang Jun.)
I'll move...
the briefcase now. Find where the car is.
(An order from the chairman)
We have to gather everyone except Bo Hyun.
For now, wait here.
Okay. Where's the car?
- It's right there. - Okay.
(Chairman Ha plans to move the money briefcase first.)
I'll take the briefcase.
Quickly look for the handcuffs.
(Team Detective is busy looking for the handcuffs.)
I found them!
(Detective Kook obtains the handcuffs.)
Look for them quickly.
It's so obvious. I have no choice now.
I found them.
(Ye Eun also found the handcuffs.)
Awesome!
Awesome.
I'll walk quickly. Stay far away from me.
(Team Detective is very close to finding all the handcuffs.)
Are there many people there?
(Running)
(Chairman Ha goes to the car while no one is around.)
(He managed to bring the money briefcase without getting caught.)
Okay. This...
(The money briefcase)
I'll keep this here. I have to get back inside now.
Let's head back.
(All that's left is gathering the tycoons in the car.)
Sang Jun.
It's a Hyundai car. Plate number 5201.
(He shares the car plate number.)
- Plate number 5201. - Tell everyone to come outside.
I'll take them.
Plate number 5201. I'll get the engine started.
(Sang Jun leaves with the chairman's orders.)
You know who to leave behind, right?
(Urgent)
Hurry, hurry! We don't have much time.
(Will Team Flex escape first, or will Team Detective arrest them?)
Hurry, Sang Jun!
We're looking for an opportunity to escape.
Hurry!
Handcuffs!
- Did you find them? - Yes.
Did you find them?
(Team Detective members gather with the handcuffs.)
Okay. Then first... Where are the handcuffs, Ye Eun?
You have them there. Okay, then first...
Once the undercover detective...
- finds the handcuffs, - Did he find them?
that's all of them. Only Se Chan hasn't found them.
- Se Chan? - Se Chan is suspicious.
Se Chan is suspicious.
I'm looking for them!
- Where is he? - I'm looking for them, Jong Kook.
Why do you keep excluding me?
I'm on the same team too. I'm a detective!
Se Chan is suspicious.
- And... - I think it's him.
The undercover detective needs to find the handcuffs.
(They exclude Se Chan...)
(and try to look for a handcuff for the undercover detective.)
Let's quickly find a pair of handcuffs and give them to Seok Jin.
Let's look for them.
I need to decide now. Will I go out with them...
(For Team Detective to win,)
(they must find all the handcuffs and arrest Haha,)
or...
(or Seok Jin, the undercover cop, must leave with Haha in the car.)
will I arrest the chairman?
I have to decide.
(Chairman Ha is waiting in the car to avoid getting arrested.)
I'll act like I'm looking for hints around here and deliver the message.
(Sang Jun is gathering the other tycoons.)
(He runs into Seok Sam, the undercover cop, by chance.)
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Why? Okay, let's talk. I love people who want to talk to me.
There's a Hyundai with plate number 2501 in the parking lot.
(He tells him the plate number right away.)
(He revealed the car plate number to the undercover detective.)
- We're leaving? - Let's escape.
- Okay. Let's go. - Ji Hyo and...
- Excluding Bo Hyun. - Excluding Bo Hyun.
(Nice.)
- Ji Hyo and... - Okay.
- Number 2501? - Yes.
(He obtained the crucial information for Team Detective to win.)
- That way. - Okay.
Where is Ji Hyo?
(If they escape with Seok Sam, Team Flex will lose.)
- What? - Where is Ji Hyo?
Ji Hyo is right there. Ji Hyo!
Just take Ji Hyo with you.
(Ji Hyo, who was searching, joins them too.)
What is it?
Come here. Hurry, Ji Hyo.
(They must get Bo Hyun in the car instead of Seok Sam.)
- We're escaping. - We're escaping.
What? Where are you going? Hey!
(Bo Hyun the real tycoon chases them when he sees them escape.)
Where are you going, you fools? Where are you going?
- Hurry up! - But Jae Seok has to come.
There's a detective among us!
Who? That's Bo Hyun!
(Where are you going without me?)
Where are you going?
You shouldn't escape now!
(Until the end)
- It's Bo Hyun. - Where are you going?
It's Bo Hyun!
Hey!
(Here!)
Here!
(If they leave with Seok Sam,)
Okay.
- Get in. - Number 5201.
(Team Flex loses.)
Hurry. Bo Hyun shouldn't get in the car.
Jae Seok should...
- If so many of us... - Goodness.
(Undercover detective Seok Jin gets in the car.)
- What is it? - We need to get in the car quickly!
- Where are you going? - Bo Hyun shouldn't get in the car.
- Not Bo Hyun. Lock the doors. - No!
- Lock the door. - How could you let him catch you?
But...
- Se Chan. - Yes?
(Meanwhile, the detectives...)
- Have you not found the handcuffs? - I haven't found them yet.
Could I search your bag to make sure?
- What? - Your bag.
(They check Ssaebssaeb's bag,)
He might have found the handcuffs...
(who is suspected of being the undercover secretary.)
You know, he suddenly said,
- "Ji Ye Eun..." - We need to find the handcuffs.
- "Jong Kook is suspicious." - Look at this!
(Is Ssaebssaeb really Team Flex's undercover secretary?)
- It's... - We...
- It was very... - We need to check.
- Why do this in front of them? - He...
- Jong Kook. - I have to search you.
(Removing his cap)
- Shin Bi. - Jong Kook.
- Why you... - Let's search...
(Removing his name tag)
Search him now.
(After making a mess out of him, they search his body.)
They're not here. This guy...
- What are you doing? - You...
- It's not me! - It's not Bo Hyun!
(Meanwhile, Team Flex is having a standoff in front of the car.)
It's not me!
- Goodness. - Goodness.
(Anxious)
- What's wrong with Ji Hyo? - What is she doing?
- What? - Jae Seok.
(At that moment, Jae Seok joins them too.)
- Jae Seok is here. - This is driving me crazy.
Haha, the detective is in the car.
- Bo Hyun is the detective. - This is so frustrating.
- He is... - The hint I found says...
- Bo Hyun is not the detective. - What's the hint?
- Hurry and get in. - What does it say?
The undercover detective is married.
- It's not me. - What?
(The undercover detective is about to get caught!)
(Ji Hyo found the hint right before they got in the car.)
- Undercover detective is married. - It's not me.
(The undercover detective is married.)
(Unmarried)
Bo Hyun is ruled out.
The undercover detective is married.
Is it Seok Jin?
What does it mean that he's married?
Hang on. Drag Seok Jin out.
(They discovered the detective right before the escape.)
- It's not you? - Wait.
- Jee Seok Jin? Come on out. - It's not me!
(Detective Seok Sam decides to hunker down.)
- It's not me! - Is it Seok Jin?
(He can't believe it.)
- It's Seok Jin. - No!
- I said he was strange. - What does that mean?
- Come on out. - Get out.
(Struggling)
- What does that hint mean? - Just drag him out.
- Lift him. - What does that mean?
(Seok Sam, who's been married for 27 years, refuses to move.)
- What does that mean? - Drag him out. Hurry.
What does that mean?
(They try to drag him out by force.)
I said Seok Jin was strange.
(He tries to contact Team Detective.)
- What do you mean? - He's making a call.
- He's calling them. - Get him out.
- This is... - His shoes.
(They miss his emergency call as they're busy searching Ssaebssaeb.)
Take off your shoes.
- Take them off. - Is this your belly?
- This is my belly. - There's nothing.
- He's calling them. - Get him out.
- Good. We ripped it off. - You got it off.
(His name tag is removed!)
- You're the detective. - No.
- What does the hint mean? - Come on out.
(He cannot move for 3 minutes.)
- What does it mean? - Just get out.
- Bo Hyun. - Bo Hyun, lift him.
- Drag him out. - Ahn Bo Hyun!
Drag Seok Jin out.
- What does the hint mean? - Drag him out.
It's not me!
- Hurry. - No!
Just get in.
(Bo Hyun overcomes his bitterness and showcases his strength.)
- Get him out. - Hang on.
- It's not me! - Hang on.
- Hurry and get in. - What does that mean?
(Team Flex starts the car after kicking out the detectie.)
- Guys! - Ditch him.
- You're being fooled. - Kick him.
Don't move.
- Guys! - Seok Jin, you're halted.
Guys!
- Hurry and come here. - Guys!
- Get in quickly. - Hey, hurry.
(Team Flex wins if they leave before Team Detective arrives.)
- Buckle up. - We got this.
- Jong Kook! - Buckle up.
That fool.
Here!
(While he can't do anything without being able to move!)
(Team Flex's car drives away.)
Buckle up.
- My goodness. - Seatbelt.
- If it weren't for Ji Hyo... - We did it.
Song Ji Hyo did it.
- Bo Hyun. - Yes.
Why were you acting so suspiciously?
(Thanks to Ji Hyo's crucial hint, Team Flex escapes successfully.)
- What was that? - Why did you do that?
Team Flex successfully escaped with the money briefcase.
(Team Flex wins.)
Team Detective and the undercover detective...
failed to arrest the chairman,
so they will receive the penalty.
Now, Team Detective...
will vote on who the undercover secretary is.
If they successfully spot the undercover secretary,
only two on Team Detective will receive the penalty.
(The undercover secretary)
It's Se Chan.
We all found this.
(Ye Eun thinks Se Chan is the secretary...)
- Is it her? - Seriously, it's not me.
(because he didn't find any handcuff.)
- But... - Is it you?
What?
I got cleaned out, you know.
Isn't it him?
It's Se Chan.
Is it her?
- It could be her. - It's not me.
- I'm serious. - I kept saying it was Haha,
but she disagreed.
I think we should rule out Ji Hyo and Haha.
- I don't think so. - It's not Ji Hyo and Haha.
- Haha... - These three.
It could be Haha.
(Jong Kook thinks she knew about Chairman Ha and covered for him.)
I don't think it's Haha.
- It's just that I had bad judgment. - Is it over once we get it right?
- I think she's blushing. - Today...
- My face is always red. - Hey.
(Ye Eun has suddenly become the prime suspect.)
I think it's her.
- It's Ye Eun. - Jong Kook, I'm telling you.
I think it's Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
(Thinking)
- I think it's Jong Kook. - Seriously, it's not me.
(Time to choose)
- This is really hard. - One...
- Who will you pick? - Ye Eun.
Ye Eun?
Time to pick the secretary. One, two, three.
(Who will the detectives choose?)
(Ye Eun gets the most votes.)
Seriously, it's not me.
Ji Ye Eun.
I chose Jong Kook.
See? I said it wasn't me.
- Are you sure you're choosing me? - Yes.
Then, I'll pick you.
I'll pick her if you don't pick me.
(Threatening)
What are you doing?
I pick you.
- Are you sure? - I choose Jong Kook.
Then I pick Ye Eun.
Jong Kook?
- It's not me. - Is it Ye Eun?
(The detectives choose Ye Eun as the undercover secretary.)
It's not me!
- Unbelievable. - Then it must be Ye Eun.
- It's not me! - I was going to talk to her.
(Is Ye Eun really the undercover secretary?)
- Ye Eun. - You'll get the penalty too.
- We all will get the penalty. - The undercover secretary...
The undercover detective.
is not Ye Eun.
- See? - See? I told you!
(Team Detective failed to catch the undercover secretary.)
- It's Jong Kook! It's not me. - All right.
(Then who among them is the undercover secretary?)
The undercover secretary should reveal their identity now.
It's Jong Kook.
- One, two, three. - Is it Eun Chae?
(Jung Eun Chae)
Darn it!
(Chairman!)
See?
(A heartwarming high five with the chairman!)
- I told you! - Is it Eun Chae?
It's unbelievable.
- Isn't it Se Chan? - How could we have found it out?
(The undercover secretary hidden among Team Detective...)
- Isn't it Se Chan? - It's not me.
(was Eun Chae!)
Isn't it you?
Let me introduce the undercover secretary...
(During Chairman Ha's opening and rule briefing)
to plant in Team Detective.
(Secretary Jung greeted Chairman Ha during the opening.)
- Hello. - Hello. I'm the Chairman.
- Okay. That's right. - Mine.
(Secretary Jung's contribution)
(Intentionally giving away points in the foot volleyball match...)
- Jung Eun Chae! - Header, Eun Chae!
(while pretending to do slapstick comedy)
(Se Chan lost his hints to Bo Hyun.)
I lost all six hints.
Isn't it that you let him steal them?
(Framing Se Chan as the spy...)
- Who? I didn't. - Bo Hyun is probably the chairman.
(to dodge suspicion herself)
- And he's the secretary. So... - Right.
(Laughing)
(And throughout the race...)
I got a text message.
I got a message from her.
(If you see me, please rip off my name tag.)
(You're being suspected for laughing when Jong Kook gave away a point.)
"You're under suspicion."
(Reporting things to the chairman and asking him to be careful)
"Please be careful."
See? She is truly loyal.
- Who will you pick? - Ye Eun.
- Ye Eun? - Yes.
(Even subtly leading the majority vote...)
Time to pick the secretary. One, two, three.
(toward Ye Eun in the final vote)
It's not Ji Ye Eun.
- See? - I told you.
(I survived.)
- I said it wasn't me! - She said it wasn't her.
She really masterminded so many things.
(The novice undercover secretary did an impressive job.)
How are we supposed to know when she barely talks?
- She's so quiet. - Why are you yelling?
(Upset)
- She talks only when she buys gold! - She only speaks when buying gold!
How would we know?
I said it wasn't me!
(Ddochi feels very wronged.)
- But... - About Eun Chae,
Jong Kook and I said this.
(Eun Chae made a fool out of the veteran detectives.)
If it's Eun Chae, there's no way we can guess it.
(Good job!)
Except for the undercover detective,
the five members of Team Detective and the undercover secretary...
(To Team Flex and Eun Chae who've won...)
will be given seasonal fruit sets and the items...
(The gift of seasonal fruit...)
purchased during the mission.
(and the items from the mission!)
That's a lot.
- I want Eun Chae to have the gold. - Okay.
The gold should go to Eun Chae.
- Congratulations. - No.
But I want this.
- This is more expensive. - Isn't this gold?
- Is this gold? - This is also gold.
She's impressive.
I didn't know Eun Chae could speak so quickly.
(Amazed)
- She's blinded by gold. - Her nickname is Gold Chae.
- This is for Sang Jun. - Okay. Sang Jun.
- Good. - Thank you.
I'll have the blanket.
(They distribute the gifts nicely.)
- Okay. You can take it. - Go ahead.
I want the cooling blanket.
Team Detective and the undercover detective...
(Team Detective and the undercover detective...)
will get the penalty.
(will get a penalty.)
Today's penalty is the fresh cream bomb.
(Today's penalty: Fresh cream bomb)
I'm scared.
One, two, three.
(Flaring)
(The clueless detectives smoothly received the penalty.)
Good work, everyone.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(We thank the "Flex X Cop" team for the satisfying fun.)
- What is this? - Where are we going?
(Mysterious board games appeared all over Seoul.)
We have to find this.
The team that completes...
- one lap first wins. - What is this?
There's a prize.
- Tablet PC. - Tablet PC.
(Super lavish prizes at stake for just a single game)
- What? I want it. - Tablet PC!
Are you giving it for real?
(Glaring)
- Hey. - It's been a while.
(The ambitious guests jumping into the game to make a fortune)
Jin Ho, you looked so slim...
when you came here last time.
- He gained a lot of weight. - He got so chubby.
(Back to his precious weight)
Did you say you were on Mounjaro back then?
(Back with a brand-new look after the shot and the yo-yo effect)
- He said he was. - I lost some weight back then.
(Hong Jin Ho)
But the yo-yo effect hit me later on.
Ready or not...
(Unlike his weight, his mouth remains unchanged.)
Seriously, what is he saying?
Rock-paper-scissors!
(The legendary former gamer isn't even good at games.)
You should open your eyes, Jin Ho!
(He's just a problem child now.)
It's so cold!
- There you go, Ji Yu. - I'm scared.
(Meanwhile, she's a hunting dog that bites into everything to win.)
(Target spotted)
Hey, don't be so harsh.
(Kim Ji Yu)
Let's go!
I told you to come forward, but why do you keep...
I don't understand a word you say.
(A single mispronunciation splits the team apart.)
- Clean out your ears then. - Clean out my ears?
(It's impossible to communicate.)
We can't communicate at all.
I'm scared.
(Forget the team. It's the full-on survival mode now.)
I might let go of the pillow and punch you with my fist.
Stop it!
- This is nice. Hey. - All of you should go.
(They hide just to survive.)
(They even refuse to be shot.)
(The dice board is filled with pure madness.)
- Please! - Four.
Please!
(A game with their lives on the line)
- Four! - Yes!
- There you go. - Let's do this.
(Who will be the final winner?)
This is the worst for us.
(Let's All Take a Tour Around Jongno)
(Running Man)